<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<playlist version="1" xmlns="http://xspf.org/ns/0/" xmlns:ov="http://www.oeta.tv/2009/ov/">
	<title>Gallery</title>
	<creator>OETA</creator>
	<annotation>OETA Emmy Award-winning series covering all aspects of Oklahoma art and culture.</annotation>
	<meta rel="generator">MetaMorphIsis at OETA</meta>
	<meta rel="generatorURL">http://www.oeta.tv</meta>
	<trackList>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 407</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Spanish Blood</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/spanishblood.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/cruz.jpg</image>
			<identifier>1551</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Spanish Blood "The Guitar of Edgar Cruz"

A man and his guitar, you’ve seen them around the state and others have heard them perform around the world. Oklahoma City’s Edgar Cruz may be more famous internationally as a fingerstyle guitarist than even here at home. We thought it was time you learned more about the man who is quickly becoming a legend. Come with us on an extraordinary journey of exploration as Gallery goes behind the guitar and into the soul of Edgar Cruz.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>50</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery Documentary</title>
			<ov:subtitle>StarDanceSwan</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/stardanceswan_FCP.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/swan_revised.jpg</image>
			<identifier>1590</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Just the company’s name evokes wonder. StarDanceSwan’s classes, workshops and performances touch and stir the creative spirit.. StarDanceSwan has gathered all ages to dream and to dance. It allows you to explore the magic that movement, music, poetry and visual arts bring into our lives. There is simply no place like it for children who want to learn the movement of dance where space, gravity, balance and energy involved in the discipline connects them to their world.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>49</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 301</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Muscle Car Ranch</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/musclecar.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/musclecar.jpg</image>
			<identifier>1591</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Oklahoma is well known for it’s cattle ranches, but one ranch in particular has a growing reputation for it’s highly respected “horsepower”. The Muscle Car Ranch in Chickasha is a tribute to chrome, cubic inches, big engines, and two decades of art dedicated to muscle cars. Curtis Hart has created the world he loves, where the colorfully powerful automobiles, known as muscle cars, continue to influence generations.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>48</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 1104</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Creativity Unearthed / Chickasaw Museum</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/gallery_1104.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/gallery_1104_thumb.jpg</image>
			<identifier>1119</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[He’s been touching generations for decades, fanning the flame of creativity wherever he finds it and along the way, he’s molded himself into the fabric of Oklahoma’s most vibrant arts district.   Collin Rosebrook is a ceramic sculptor and steel artist who moved into the Paseo Arts District before it was cool.  His work is masterful and, as Rosebrook proudly explains, affordable.  

Plus, Gallery takes you on a tour of the Chickasaw Musuem in Sulphur, Oklahoma.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>47</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 1103</title>
			<ov:subtitle>The Way Love Goes</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/gallery1103.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/l1103_lovegoes.jpg</image>
			<identifier>948</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[In this full episode of Gallery we feature country artist Wade Hayes and family. We travel to Bethel Acres for the Friends Day Festival. A look at how a small town coped with loss of lives in their community and how Wade and his parents have played an important role.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>44</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 1103</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Wade &amp; Don Hayes</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/hayespickup_g1103.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/hayespickup_g1103.jpg</image>
			<identifier>916</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[In this video extra, Don Hayes and son, Country Artist Wade Hayes rehearse on back of Don's truck before the "Friends Day' festival in Bethel Acres.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>41</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 1101</title>
			<ov:subtitle>The Skullmaster / Atrocity</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/galleryshow1101.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/gallerylogo.jpg</image>
			<identifier>857</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[These are just a few of the horrible moments in history portrayed on canvas by Oklahoma artist Eric Humphries.    Humphries, who calls himself an artistic historian, turned his attention to portraying atrocities over a decade ago and in doing so, found his purpose…his artistic voice. 
Plus, 
Sticks and stones, toys and bones...interpretation is left to the beholder.   Behold the work of The Skull Master, Joey Williams on the July installment of Gallery. Williams, was raised in the heart of the Bible belt, but grew up pushing the envelope of his conservative surroundings

Plus, Gallery visits Eric Humphries, who calls himself an artistic historian, turned his attention to portraying atrocities over a decade ago and in doing so, found his purpose…his artistic voice.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>29</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 1009</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Amazing Dave / Sam Noble Museum</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/gallery1009.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/gallerylogo.jpg</image>
			<identifier>828</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[THE AMAZING DAVE MAY

He’s known as The Amazing Dave May by Oklahoma audiences who’ve seen his vaudeville-esque ventriloquist and magic road show.  He’s known as May Day in the Morning on KLOR 99.3 FM in Ponca City.   He’s known as the Executive Director of The Poncan Theatre and he’s known as the man who discovered the world’s largest collection of hand painted movie theater poster art in the world.  
He’s a renaissance man with boundless energy and we found out why Ponca City and Oklahomans around the state can’t help but stand up and cheer for The Amazing Dave May. Plus, It took a century to build, but today it’s a global model and it’s right here in Oklahoma.    Join Gallery in June as we take you to the Sam Noble Museum of Natural History in Norman.     The facility is state of the art, but the collection is millions of years old, preserved through the last hundred years in barracks, barns and stables.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>28</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 1008</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Red Cedar Creations / China Painters</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/Gallery1008FiNAL.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/gallerylogo.jpg</image>
			<identifier>758</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[He graduated from the Berklee School of Music in Boston and returned home to Fairview, Oklahoma to perform across the state and to build guitars.  See Tony Rincon on stage and behind the scenes to see craftsmanship of his instruments with bodies made from Easter Red Cedar, the same wood his parents used to create custom coffins and caskets out of the same workshop.
Plus, The World Organization of China Painters has made Oklahoma a mecca for China artists around the world.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>27</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery  1007</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Culinary Arts</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/gallery1007revised.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/gallerylogo.jpg</image>
			<identifier>732</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The empty plate is a blank canvas for culinary artists and their medium is food.  Oklahoma is on the cusp of a cultural renaissance and this form of expression is part of the experience.   Gallery takes you to the top culinary school in the state, where chefs who’ve worked all over the world are teaching the next generation what it takes to be the best in their field…or in the kitchen.  The Culinary Institute at Platt College is prepping for a regional competition that will put them head to head against other culinary schools from 15 states.  Last year they took bronze.  This year, the team is going for gold.  See what it takes to julienne, dice, grate, pare and peel your way to super star status at the stove as we go behind the scenes at one of the most high pressure art studios we’ve ever visited…the Kitchens of the culinary arts.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>26</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 1006</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Functional Fusion / Toy Story</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/gallery1006.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/gallerylogo.jpg</image>
			<identifier>656</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[They’re used to working alone.  They’re used to bringing their ideas to life unhindered by restrictions.   They’re used to being singularly accomplished artists in their individual fields, but when they’re thrown together to carry out a common mission full of regulations, there’s no telling what these Oklahoma artists will come up with.  State art maven, Laura Warriner knew it would be wonderful, but challenging when she asked 50 Oklahoma creatives to design artistic and functional furniture for an entire house.   The process was exhausting, but the results?  You won’t believe just how artistic your home furnishings could be. Plus, "Toy Story", model trains and airplanes are not just for the young, but can be a hobby that last a lifetime. Gallery visits model enthusiasts with vast collections of trains and layouts which they have been collecting since childhood.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>25</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title> 1006 Extra</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Train Sizes</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/trainsizes4by3.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/trainsizes4by3.jpg</image>
			<identifier>655</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Many model train enthusiasts spend lots of time and money collecting and running model trains. Kevin Huffman, model railroad collector and salesman at OKC Whistle Stop shows us the difference in sizes, types, and the most popular scale for the beginning model train collector.</p>]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>24</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 1005</title>
			<ov:subtitle>The Thespian / Taxidermy</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/gallery1005.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/gallerylogo.jpg</image>
			<identifier>639</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[He trained on stages in Oklahoma, then took to stages around the world starring in national Broadway tours and headlining in theatres in all 50 states.  Now Jonathan Beck Reed has come home to start a family and to give back.  Reed and his old college friends operate one of only two union theatres in the state.  He teaches acting at Oklahoma City University and runs a private studio for younger students in Edmond.   He was born to be onstage and Oklahoma is lucky he was born here because after being away for 12 years, The Thespian has come home.
Plus, He’s a national leader in his field attracting patrons from near and far.  Choctaw‘s Danny Keener is just one of two Master of Master taxidermists in Oklahoma.  The retired Oklahoma City police officer of 28 years has a knack for  Well, let’s just say Keener is an expert in all the skills required to engage in The Art of Preservation.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>23</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 1004</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Brick by Brick</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/gallery1004.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/gallerylogo.jpg</image>
			<identifier>638</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[After months of painstaking work, brick artist (Lego bricks, that is) Kurt Zimmerle is back home in Michigan working on his Halloween haunted houses. What he’s left behind is a masterpiece that will benefit Oklahoma City’s poverty stricken children for years to come.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>22</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 1003</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Show Promo</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/gallerypromo1003.flv</location>
			<image>/images/stories/gallery/images/beyondmetal.jpg</image>
			<identifier>445</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Artist Stan Carroll]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>21</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 1003</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Beyond Metal / McSwain</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/gallery1003.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/gallerylogo.jpg</image>
			<identifier>637</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Beyond Metal is a Design Workshop, founded by Stan Carroll, in 1998 as a full service sculpture, architecture, furniture, and architectural metals design and fabrication firm.   Throughout 25 years of  practice, Carroll’s philosophy has developed as a challenge to create harmony between form and function.
Plus, A "McSwain Revival", An Oklahoma landmark has a new lease on life thanks to the Chickasaw Nation.  The McSwain Theatre in Ada is a 90 year old icon that is now a state of the art live entertainment venue.   Once a venue for Vaudeville, the old theatre has a new lease on life and she’s more popular than ever.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>20</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 1002</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Show Promo</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/gallerypromo1002.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/gallerypromo1002.jpg</image>
			<identifier>417</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Promotional Video for Gallery 1002]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>19</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 1002</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Sunspots</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/gallery1002.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/gallerylogo.jpg</image>
			<identifier>636</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[An Emmy award winning episode about 12 green teenagers who team up with a seasoned Hollywood actor, writer and producer to try to make a movie in just one week?  

Don’t miss the drama, the comedy and the out and out wacky shenanigans when Gallery takes you behind the scenes for “The Making of:  Sunspots”.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>18</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 1001</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Breaking the Mold</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/gallery1001.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/gallerylogo.jpg</image>
			<identifier>341</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Step inside the studio of sculptor, carver and molding artist Kendall Howerton.   His work is on display across the country in national retail stores and commercial buildings, but his latest project hits closer to home.    Howerton is putting his talent to work to increase Breast Cancer Awareness in Oklahoma and to raise money for the cause.  He is using Oklahoma models for his latest creations, pink ribbons cast from the bodies of the models who, themselves, are breast cancer survivors.  

Gallery brings its audience into the very personal, artistic work of Howerton and a breast cancer survivor who has decided to share her story and her scars with the world through Howerton’s art.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>16</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 909</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Show Promo</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/rockopen.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/gallery909.jpg</image>
			<identifier>187</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Oklahoma Rocks Show Promo]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>15</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 909</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Oklahoma Rocks</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/gallery909.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/gallerylogo.jpg</image>
			<identifier>185</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[OETA’S Emmy Award winning documentary series, “Gallery”, will rock it’s viewers in June as it covers the opening of a hot new exhibit at the Oklahoma History Center. 

 Another Hot Oklahoma Night” shines the spotlight on Oklahoma artists who have made major contributions to that uniquely American music genre, Rock and Roll. 

The History Center has gathered stories and artifacts from 150 artists and innovators like The Collins Kids of Tahlequah, who, along with Wanda Jackson are considered artists who nurtured the birth of Rock.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>14</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>909 Extra</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Flaming Lips</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/flaminglips.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/flaminglips.jpg</image>
			<identifier>188</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[<p>Wayne Coyne of the Flaming Lips.</p>]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>13</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 908</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Transitions / Shaping LIfe</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/gallery908.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/gallerylogo.jpg</image>
			<identifier>178</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Move over Indiana Jones!    Oklahoma has its own mild mannered art historian who has traveled the world and skirted the bad guys to bring home mementoes worth millions!  As a private curator for Oklahoma businessmen, Jon Burris has witnessed the cultural-revolution in China and the slow emergence of the art culture in Russia.
Plus, Art is the fusion of one's experience, the elements of design and quality materials. All of this is driven by the creative idea and craftsmanship
Glen Thomas began drawing when he was four and does not show signs of tiring of this activity. Glen is also a teacher who has taught hundreds of students, shaping their minds and lives with his art teachings.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>12</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery  907</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Subjective Horse / Metal Mangler</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/galleryshow907.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/gallerylogo.jpg</image>
			<identifier>182</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[She is an Oklahoma artist who’s work is well known nationwide.  Jean Richardson paints the horse in abstract, though say it is impressionism.  Her paintings are large and subjective.  For Richardson, her horses are not horses, they are a metaphor for the human spirit.   A wall covering work can be about a single word, power, freedom, solitude or exhilaration.   But no matter what the word is, the work is ultimately about Richardson, who she is and where she is in her life.
Plus, You don’t have to go to Orange County California to find a cutting edge motorcycle builder! Oklahoma has its own chopper artist in Bethany.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>10</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 906</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Sweet Rewards</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/CakeShow.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/gallerylogo.jpg</image>
			<identifier>152</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Their art is crisp and layered, demanding and colorful, sweet and….delicious.  

We’re talking about Sugar Artists.    They come from all over the world to Tulsa, Oklahoma each year for the Grand National Wedding Cake Competition.    Never has the perfect creation of an edible flower been so crucial, the placement of a sugar ribbon so nerve wracking or the stacking of carefully cultivated layers so vital.  And if that isn’t enough pressure, how about the prospect of transporting these oh so sweet creations cross country, some across oceans, to compete with world masters?]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>9</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 905</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Song Receiver</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/dennisjernigan.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/song_reciever.jpg</image>
			<identifier>1540</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Join Gallery as we step into the world of a major Christian Artist who says he is not a songwriter but a song receiver. An inspirational story about the life and music of Dennis Jernigan.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>8</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 804</title>
			<ov:subtitle>The Singing Fisherman</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/mikecrowley.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/singing_fisherman.jpg</image>
			<identifier>1548</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[His voice once echoed around the world, now it skips across the waters of Lake Hefner. An amazing story of the life and song of Mike Crowley.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>7</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 504</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Santa Dan's Mustard Seeds</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/santadan.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/santadan.jpg</image>
			<identifier>1542</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[CHRISTMAS SPECIAL<br>
He is one of America’s “real life Santas.” No glue-on whiskers or foam pillows for this Santa, his beard and his belly are real. So is his message to Oklahoma children. Find out the extraordinary story of a man known to his neighbors as Dan and to children around the state as “Santa.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>6</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 801</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Bass Society</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/bass.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/bass_society.jpg</image>
			<identifier>1554</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The World of Bass who traveled to Oklahoma City for the International Society of Bassists
Convention. This convention was the first gathering of it's kind in Oklahoma, but for the artists
who came from more than 20 countries to attend, it was a homecoming , a chance to see
fellow players who are brothers and sisters in the "Bassist" sense.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>5</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 304</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Lee Shaw</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/leeshaw.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/leeshaw.jpg</image>
			<identifier>1556</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[She’s been playing the piano for parts of eight decades and is considered one of the most influential female jazz pianists of all time. She was inducted into the Oklahoma Jazz Hall of Fame in 1993. Lee Shaw grew up in Ada and has performed around the world with her Lee Shaw Trio. She has shared the stage with jazz greats like Sara Vaughan and Billie Holiday. These days, she spends most of her time teaching at her home near Albany, New York and is on the staff at Albany’s College of St. Rose. But once in a while she takes her trio on the road to perform at venues around the Country. Lee recently took the stage at UCO Jazz Lab in Edmond and that’s where our Gallery crew caught up with her for an in-depth interview and a look at her wonderful career.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>4</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 304</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Double Star Studio</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/doublestar.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/doulblestar.jpg</image>
			<identifier>1555</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Sheldon is an award-winning author, whose interest in Oklahoma and it’s history, has led to four colorfully exciting books. Nancy, a renowned sculptor,didn’t discover her true creative heart until twenty years into her marriage until one day, Sheldon, hot into a writing surge, worked into a coffee break and encouraged her to some whittling while she waited for his frenzy to cool. When Sheldon emerged for that cup of java, he and Nancy discovered a whole new aspect of their lives.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>3</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 201</title>
			<ov:subtitle>&quot;It Ain't Shakespeare&quot;</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/kent.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/kentrollins.jpg</image>
			<identifier>1553</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Kent Rollins loves the cowboy way of life. He is a cowboy, works as a cowboy, and as a weather toughened, dust eating, horse riding cowboy, and he writes poetry. Through words caressed by those beautiful Oklahoma sunrises and sunsets, he wants you to experience the heritage and humor he takes with him every time he saddles up to meet the fresh air of Oklahoma’s Great Plains Country.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>2</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Gallery 101</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Long Way Home</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/longwayhome.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/gallery/_thumbs/longway.jpg</image>
			<identifier>1550</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Everyone has been touched by someone or some place while walking down the path to our futures. Artist and native Oklahoman, Melvin Smith, wants you to meet people and places that shaped his life. It's an interesting journey through sculpture and collage, color and emotion, the artist uses known in the art world as found object. Gallery goes beyond Melvin Smiths wonderful African masks that hang so bodly on the wall of his studio and museum to capture the inner workings of this sculptor and reveal the passion thats goes into each piece he creates.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>1</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
	</trackList>
</playlist>
