<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<playlist version="1" xmlns="http://xspf.org/ns/0/" xmlns:ov="http://www.oeta.tv/2009/ov/">
	<title>OKC Metro</title>
	<creator>OETA</creator>
	<annotation>&quot;OKC Metro&quot; is a weekly, half-hour public affairs interview program highlighting events and groups in the Oklahoma City metropolitan area.</annotation>
	<meta rel="generator">MetaMorphIsis at OETA</meta>
	<meta rel="generatorURL">http://www.oeta.tv</meta>
	<trackList>
		<track>
			<title>OKC Metro</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Final Metro: Col. James Wilhite, 211 Oklahoma</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/Metro_062610.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/_thumbs/Metro_062610.jpg</image>
			<identifier>844</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Due to budget cuts, this is our final production of OKC Metro. We look at the war in Afghanistan through the eyes of Colonel James Wilhite. He tells us how he, and others, "Answered the Call" to serve this country in a place very far away and in very dire straits. We'll also tell you about a wonderful statewide referral center that helps Oklahomans "get connected." And we'll say a final "goodbye" to YOU for the last time...]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>26</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>OKC Metro</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Red Earth, OKC Parks, Carolyn Hart, EMMY nominations</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/Metro_061210.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/_thumbs/Metro_061210.jpg</image>
			<identifier>826</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[We give you details about one of the country's premiere Native American Cultural festivals. If you're looking for a great place to spend time with your kids, we'll tell you how to get the most out of Oklahoma City's public parks. And if you want to "chill out" with a good book, we'll introduce you to a metro author who just "loves" a good mystery. And we share big news about two EMMY nominations for OKC Metro!]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>25</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>OKC Metro</title>
			<ov:subtitle>AARP, Generation Y, OKC CoCo</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/Metro_060510.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/_thumbs/Metro_060510.jpg</image>
			<identifier>820</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Our topics are money, unemployment, debt, and new ways of doing business. We talk about the strain put on workers over the age of fifty, many of whom have recently lost their jobs. Then we visit with a consumer credit counselor about the warning signs that "Generation Y" is drowning in debt. And finally, we tell you how a new co-working collaborative may be the "next big thing" in business.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>24</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>OKC Metro</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Aerospace, Charlie Christian, [Artspace] at Untitled, Carolyn Hill</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/Metro_052210.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/_thumbs/Metro_052210.jpg</image>
			<identifier>800</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[We look at the 12-billion dollar impact the aerospace industry has on our state. For jazz fans, we give you the scoop on the Charlie Christian Jazz Festival, and meet the author of a wonderful new book about Christian's life and music. We also get a peek at a great exhibit at Artspace at Untitled. And we bid a fond farewell to a metro woman who advocated for the arts all her life.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>23</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>OKC Metro</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Stroke Awareness, DRS Visual Services, Richard Rush</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/Metro_050810.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/_thumbs/Metro_050810.jpg</image>
			<identifier>768</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[We tell you about the five major warning signs of stroke and meet a stroke survivor. Then we introduce you to two "differently-abled" guests who serve people with vision difficulties, but neither of them lets their own blindness slow them down. And the recently-retired President of the State Chamber of Commerce offers his view of what Oklahoma needs to do to grow its economy.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>21</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>OKC Metro</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Sandy Coats, Oklahoma School of Science &amp; Math</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/Metro_050110_good.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/_thumbs/Metro_050110_good.jpg</image>
			<identifier>749</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[U.S. Attorney Sandy Coats talks about his commitment to protecting children, and how the 1995 bombing of the Murrah Building changed his life. Dr. Edna Manning with the Oklahoma School of Science and Mathematics tells us about the astounding success rate of OSSM students.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>20</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>OKC Metro</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Catholic Charities, Red Earth Museum</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/Metro_042410.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/_thumbs/Metro_042410.jpg</image>
			<identifier>734</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[An old church is bringing new hope to homeless women in south Oklahoma City, and one of this country's finest Native American art collections can be seen at the Red Earth Museum in Oklahoma City.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>19</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>OKC Metro</title>
			<ov:subtitle>OKC Zoo, OKC Festival of the Arts, DRS Award</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/Metro_041710.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/_thumbs/Metro_041710.jpg</image>
			<identifier>726</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The new multi-million dollar Children's Zoo is now open at the Oklahoma City Zoo. We also have the latest on the annual springtime ritual, the Festival of the Arts. And we share our pride at having won the Excellence in Communication Award from the Oklahoma Department of Rehabilitation Services.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>18</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>OKC Metro</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Leona Mitchell</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/Metro_040310_revised.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/_thumbs/Metro_040310_revised.jpg</image>
			<identifier>715</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The remarkable Leona Mitchell joins us for the full half-hour. Mitchell's brilliant soprano took the opera world by storm in 1973. She shares stories of growing up in Enid, singing in her father's church, traveling the world, and winning nearly every accolade possible by one performer.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>16</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>OKC Metro</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Jim Barnes, Jeanetta Calhoun Mish, Kenneth Hada</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/Metro_032710.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/_thumbs/Metro_032710.jpg</image>
			<identifier>705</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Oklahoma's Poet Laureate tells us why he believes poetry is still vital in our high-tech, fast-moving society. Poets, Jeanetta Calhoun Mish and Kenneth Hada, tell us about the Scissortail Creative Writing Festival, held each year at East Central University in Ada.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>15</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>OKC Metro</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Music Special</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/All_Music_Metro.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/_thumbs/All_Music_Metro.jpg</image>
			<identifier>690</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[We feature Oklahoma-grown artists in this "all music" special. Ann-Janette, the Joe Settlemires Quartet, Edgar Cruz, and Wally Brown share their musical talents with us.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>14</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>OKC Metro</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Platt College, Chickasaw Elders</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/Metro_022710.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/_thumbs/Metro_022710.jpg</image>
			<identifier>680</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[We meet the President of a metro college whose priority is helping students choose, and achieve, a life of significance. We also visit with a very successful husband-and-wife team whose latest creative project pays tribute to the elders of the Chickasaw Nation.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>13</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>OKC Metro</title>
			<ov:subtitle>Voting Rights, Oklahoma Territorial Museum</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/Metro_013010.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/okc_metro/_thumbs/Metro_013010.jpg</image>
			<identifier>648</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[We pay tribute to the sacrifices and triumphs of African-Americans. We focus on the success of voting rights in the South, and how that eventually led to the election of President Obama. We have a poetry reading from acclaimed African-American poet, Lucille Clifton, and we learn more about the African-American experience during Oklahoma's territorial days. In observance of "Black History Month," Metro producer Debra Martin put together a photo essay of some of the milestones in the struggle for civil rights in America.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>10</trackNum>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
	</trackList>
</playlist>
