<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<playlist version="1" xmlns="http://xspf.org/ns/0/" xmlns:ov="http://www.oeta.tv/2009/ov/">
	<title>Oklahoma News Report</title>
	<creator>OETA</creator>
	<annotation>Featured content from the OETA Oklahoma News Report</annotation>
	<meta rel="generator">MetaMorphIsis at OETA</meta>
	<meta rel="generatorURL">http://www.oeta.tv</meta>
	<trackList>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 4-23-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_04-23-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_04-23-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>745</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Governor Henry veto's a pair of anti-abortion bills saying they are constitutionally flawed.  One would force a woman to undergo an ultrasound and listen to a detailed description of the fetus.  The other would have prohibited a woman from suing a doctor for withholding information or giving inaccurate information about her pregnancy. 

 Speaking at an event in Stillwater honoring outgoing Superintendent of Public Instruction Sandy Garrett, Governor Henry called on school teachers to lobby lawmakers.  He wants teachers to convince legislators to enact fee hikes and other budget proposals instead of making more budget cuts, especially for education. 

 Another sign that the nation's and Oklahoma's economy is turning around.  Leisure travel is increasing after falling flat for the last two years. 

 The story of Edmond high school students who raised more than half a million dollars to help cure children with cancer. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>207</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 04-21-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_4-21-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_4-21-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>736</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The Oklahoma House has rejected a bill that would have charged a heath access fee of health insurance companies to fund the states Insure Oklahoma plan.   Insure Oklahoma is the states effort to expand health care coverage to the uninsured. 

More warnings today for state lawmakers of what will happen if 10% or higher budget cuts continue into fiscal year 2011.  District Attorney's from around the state are warning that such cuts compromise public safety. 

Mental health officials warn that ongoing budget cuts will send up to 5,000 more inmates to state prisons and increase the suicide rate. 

In-Depth tonight we discuss the rules for the newest stimulus act program, rebates for buying new energy efficient home appliances. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>206</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 04-20-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_04-20-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_04-20-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>742</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[House Speaker Chris Benge and Senate President Pro Temp Glenn Coffee say they will file their own lawsuit to try and block the Health Care Reform Act.  They also don't want the Attorney General handling the case. 

A series of five anti-abortion bills easily cleared the state Senate this week.  They were originally part of a single bill that was declared unconstitutional by the state Supreme Court. 

In-Depth tonight, debate from the floor of the state Senate over a resolution that says state's are in charge of regulating health care, not the federal government. 

If Oklahoma's Sam Bradford is picked first in the NFL draft this week, O.U. would join and exclusive club.  Notre Dame is the only other school to have players drafted first in the same year by the NBA and the NFL.  
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>205</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 4-19-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_04-19-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_04-19-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>733</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[A special report on the anniversary ceremony. 

A re-broadcast of the original Oklahoma New Report coverage of the attack. 
A live interview with Charles Newcomb, the OETA reporter on the scene that day. 

Discussion with an Oklahoman who was just a child the day of the bombing and lost a family member in what remains the deadliest act of domestic terrorism in the nation's history. 

How Oklahoma school children learn now about the attack and what will change under a new state law.  
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>204</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 04-19-1995</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/bombing_day_one.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/bombing_day_one.jpg</image>
			<identifier>730</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Excerpt from coverage of the bombing of the Murrah Building in Oklahoma City]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>203</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 4-16-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_4-16-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_4-16-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>741</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>202</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 04-05-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_04-05-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_04-05-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>727</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Governor Brad Henry has been busy signing into law,  bills passed by the legislature.  That has included three anti-abortion bills that were part of an earlier law that was struck down by the state Supreme Court. 

Furloughs and layoffs are now being considered for employees of the Oklahoma Court of Criminal Appeals.  Court officials say if the cutback for next fiscal year matches those of this year, it will mean furlough days and reductions in force starting on July 1st. 

A new poll shows that more than 62-percent of Oklahomans trust the accuracy of reporting by local news media.  Most Oklahomans still get their news from television. 

Oklahoma's economy is running like a car with a nail in one tire.  The analogy offered by the Economic Development Generating Excellence policy board.  We talk In-Depth on their conclusion that it is time to rethink economic development in the state. 

And we meet a 7-year old girl who set the record this year for selling the most Girl Scout Cookies-more than 5,000 boxes. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>201</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 04-02-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_04-02-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_04-02-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>724</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Attorney General Drew Edmondson is intervening in a judge's decision that left four girls in the custody of adoptive parents who were convicted of sexually abusing a fifth child.  

Governor Henry is one of 30 governors' across the country that received a letter from an anti-government group,  demanding that he leave office within three days or be removed.  The FBI says they do not see any security threat in the letters. 

The Oklahoma division of  Disabled American Veterans offers a free transportation service to vets who for whatever reason are unable to get to V.A. Medical facilities for treatment.  The group is now issuing a public request for volunteer drivers.  We talk In-Depth about the service and their needs. 

In Business Today, a feature report on an Oklahoma company that is providing produce to thousands of stores in states across the country.  An inside look at J-M Farms in Miami. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>200</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 04-01-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_04-01-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_04-01-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>723</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The House Rules Committee has put on hold a resolution calling for the Attorney General to file suit to stop the new health care law from taking effect.   

Senate staffers have now been told they will have to take 12 unpaid furlough days or take voluntary buyouts.  Meanwhile, the House has a reported $4-million dollar bank account balance. 

At his town hall meeting in Pryor, U.S. Senator Tom Coburn talked to Angela Rosecrans about Ethics and IRS complaints filed against him over low rent he pays for accommodations where he and other lawmakers live.  At issue are artificially low rental payments because the property is listed as a church. 

Legislative committees have given approval to a pair of bills involving guns.  One would allow people with licenses to openly carry guns, the other would exempt Oklahoma made weapons and ammunition from federal regulation. 



]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>199</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-30-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_03-30-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_03-30-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>717</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The discovery of the bodies of a missing 7-year old Oklahoma girl and her stepfather apparently closes the case of a double murder-suicide.  Aja Johnson was kidnapped by Lester Hobbs in late January.  Their bodies were found in a car outside of Norman on Monday. 

Leaders from several Oklahoma Indian tribes are meeting in Tulsa today, to begin discussions on how to foster better relations with the Federal Government. 

State Budget cuts are forcing the closure of 17 child guidance centers run by the state Health Department. The centers worked with children who have speech, hearing, behavioral and developmental problems. 

The Oklahoma Blood Institute issues an urgent plea for donors.  The states blood supply is at a critically low level, now down to less than a 2-day supply. 

The President signs into law a bill that not only finalizes the health care overhaul but makes the government the lender for all college loans.  We talk with an expert on what that means for students. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>198</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-29-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_03-29-10_Sm.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_03-29-10_Sm.jpg</image>
			<identifier>714</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The Office of Juvenile Affairs is looking at layoffs and employee buyouts at the L.E. Rader center to deal with ongoing budget cuts.  The agency is trying to reduce the number of juveniles at the center to about 70. 

Attorney General Drew Edmondson is calling upon Congresswoman Mary Fallin to ratchet down the rhetoric against the health care law pointing to vandalism and threats against members of congress.  Fallin in a speech today promised to block the law from going into effect in Oklahoma.  Both are candidates for governor. 

A federal judge has turned down a request for access to secret CIA documents on the Oklahoma City bombing.  

Roadside food vendors are becoming very common place around the state.  Now local health departments are cracking down and shutting down many of those food stands for health violations. ]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>197</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-26-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_03-26-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_03-26-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>708</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[33-year old highway patrol trooper Barry Rowland of Bixby has pleaded no contest to charges he kicked a handcuffed woman.  Rowland received a one year deferred sentence and resigned from the OHP. 

Grandfield public schools are the latest to go to a four day school week to save money.  The move will save the district about $100,000 in salaries and 20% more on utility and transportation bills. 

The CSpan civic bus makes a stop in Oklahoma to hand out awards for documentaries produced by young filmmakers at Jenks High School, including top honors for junior Crystal Kayiza.

We talk In-Depth with the head of the Oklahoma Historical Society about the new Encyclopedia of Oklahoma History and Culture. ]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>196</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-25-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_03-25-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_03-25-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>706</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Several bills to further restrict abortions have cleared a Senate committee.  The measures originally were part of a bill was struck down by the state Supreme Court because there were combined into one measure. 

Senate President Pro Tem Glenn Coffee confirms that budget cuts will mean furloughs of senate staff probably after the end of the legislative session. 
 
A new report on the Oklahoma foster care system shows basic failures in caring for children who are victims of abuse or neglect.  It was filed in an ongoing federal court lawsuit against DHS. 

Census officials are warning of a scam where people pass out bogus forms that ask for social security numbers.  Six Oklahomans have reported finding the forms on their doorsteps.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>195</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-24-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_03-24-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_03-24-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>704</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[State Rep. Rebecca Hamilton says she is concerned that her bill to make it illegal for women to sell their eggs is in trouble in the state Senate.  She has now enlisted the support of anti-abortion activists to help lobby senators to move the bill along. 

Oklahoma U.S. Senator Tom Coburn says republicans can't stop the new health care law from taking effect, but they may be able to slow it down a bit.  Coburn has introduced a number of amendments to the reconciliation bill.  

Oklahoma U.S. Senator Jim Inhofe has offered amendments also.  His plan involves removing taxes on certain medical supplies. 

Using funds from a FEMA grant, a tornado shelter is being built at a Muskogee Public School.  When not protecting students from severe weather, the safe room will house a computer class. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>194</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-23-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_03-23-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_03-23-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>703</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The state Senate has easily passed a resolution that would put to a vote of the people a measure that would allow the state to opt out of health care reform, signed into law today by President Obama. 

In Depth, Cathy Tatom talked to Insurance Commissioner Kim Holland about the implementation of the new health care law. 

A new poll shows that a majority of Oklahomans favors banning smoking in bars and restaurants. 

Three anti-abortion bills are headed to the House floor after passing out of committee. 

We'll learn about new gene therapies that can be applied directly to cells. 
Some big yellow school buses are going green.  We'll show you how they are doing it. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>193</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-22-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_03-22-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_03-22-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>702</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Republicans in the state House and Senate are urging the attorney general to sue the United States to block the health care reform bill passed by the U.S. House of Representatives on Sunday night. 

In a Newsmaker Interview, we talked to Oklahoma Attorney General Drew Edmondson about the health care bill and whether his office plans to join other state attorneys general in challenging the constitutionality of the health reform legislation. 

We previewed Monday night's Tulsa School Board meeting at which a proposal to cut 7% of the district's teaching positions was discussed. 

Meantime, the Cherokee Nation of Oklahoma has announced a gift of almost three million dollars to benefit schools in northeastern Oklahoma. 

And on Sunup Clinton Griffiths featured another report on no-till farming.
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>192</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-19-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_03-19-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_03-19-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>701</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Cathy Tatom told us an increase in oil and natural gas prices may affect the affordability of housing in Oklahoma, as home values are increasing.

 U.S. Senator Tom Coburn has introduced legislation that would prevent automatic Congressional pay raises until the federal budget is balanced.

  Meningitis vaccines are underway for all students and staff in the Oologah-Talala School District.

 Angela Rosecrans went to the Tulsa Zoo, where hundreds of families were spending the last day of spring break enjoying the weather and a new exhibit.

  In Depth, we interviewed humorist Preacher Moss, in Oklahoma City for the annual Council on American-Islamic Relations banquet.

  In our Oklahoma Horizon franchise segment we met a metal sculptor in Medicine Park.

]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>191</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-18-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_03-18-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_03-18-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>700</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Just how open is government in Oklahoma?  As part of the ongoing special series of reports during Sunshine Week, we examine where government is doing a good job of providing access and where improvement is needed. 

The EPA is launching a study into the practice of hydraulic fracturing. It's a process used by natural gas producers to extract supplies from shale formations.  We talk In-Depth with Corporation Commissioner Bob Anthony.
 
The city of Tulsa is launching a new program to comply with requirements in the Americans with Disabilities Act. 

Oklahoma City, Tulsa and several other communities are making application to take part in the new super high speed internet test system being developed by Google. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>190</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-17-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_03-17-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_03-17-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>699</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The 10 Commandments monument on the grounds of the Haskell County Courthouse in Stigler was moved today to the local American Legion building.  The U.S. Supreme court let stand a lower court ruling that the monument violated separation of church and state. 

A one year old boy is now in a Tulsa hospital being testing for meningitis.  The child was moved from a hospital in Claremore but it is not yet clear if the case is related to an outbreak in the Oologah-Talala public schools. 

The Census forms are showing up in mail boxes across the state.  The forms are very easy to fill out and tonight we sit down with an expert to show just how easy it really is. 

How open is local and state government?  What steps have been taken to improve taxpayer's access to public records and public meetings?  What else can be done?  Questions we answer tonight in our special Sunshine Week series on openness in government. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>189</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-16-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_03-16-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_03-16-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>698</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Another student in the Oologah-Talala school district has developed meningitis.  The teenage girl is the seventh case in the district.  Two children have died and four others remain hospitalized. 

Another study is pointing to Oklahoma's pension plans as being seriously under-funded.  The Institute for Truth in Accounting report shows the states budget has not been balanced for years because of the growing unfunded liability now approaching $15-billion. 

Why is the legislature exempt from the states Open Meetings and Open Records Acts?  There is increasing sentiment at the state capitol for the exemption to be removed. 

An Oklahoma tele-communications company gets a big federal grant to expand broadband internet services into rural parts of Oklahoma and Kansas.  ]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>188</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-15-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_03-15-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_03-15-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>697</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The Osage Nation is continuing to appeal a lawsuit that argues Osage County is really their reservation and so tribal members cannot be taxed by the state.
 
Tulsa Hispanic leaders are urging voters to call lawmakers in opposition to house bill 3384 which would require school districts to track undocumented Hispanic children attending public schools. 

An author of two bills creating special task forces, to among other things look into health care reform, now says he will remove a provision that the panels work in secret. 

A grant from the U.S. Department of Agriculture is going to western Oklahoma to improve transportation options. ]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>187</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-12-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_03-12-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_03-12-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>696</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Two children are dead another is near death in a hospital and three others are hospitalized with more possible cases of meningitis under investigation in the Oologah-Talala School District.   
 
The Skiatook School Board has voted to fire Superintendent Gary Johnson following a state audit that showed over a half a million dollars in school funds wasted on overpriced janitorial and other supplies. 

A young Oklahoma woman has died from complications of the H1-N1 flu virus.  43 people have died from swine flu in the state. 

From scams to unclaimed refunds, we talk In-Depth with an IRS official as the tax deadline draws near. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>186</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-11-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_03-11-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_03-11-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>695</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[ Among the many bills being approved by lawmakers today, the House of Representatives approved a bill requiring both pre-martial and divorce counseling and eliminating Â“common-law marriagesÂ”. 

The Federal Reserve is warning Oklahomans to beware of new scams that target people who are in foreclosure proceedings or about to be.  The scams offer ways to get out of foreclosure, for a fee. 

Devon Energy Corporation has sold off the last of its international assets to B-P. The deal carries a $7-billion price tag.  B-P gets rights to 10 offshore exploration blocks in Brazil plus assets in the Gulf of Mexico and the Caspian Sea. 

In-Depth tonight, a discussion with Jimmy Wayne, a country music recording artist who is walking across America to draw attention to the needs of foster children who Â“age outÂ” of the program. ]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>185</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-10-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_03-10-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_03-10-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>694</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The crush of bills facing the Oklahoma House and Senate likely means late night sessions for both bodies tonight.  Thursday is the deadline for bills to leave their house of origin or they cannot be brought up again this session. 
Among the measures clearing the Senate so far today includes a proposal to restrict use of the so-called abortion pill RU 486. 

The latest unemployment numbers for the state are due out today.  We talk In-Depth with the chief economist for the state Employment Security Commission about the latest figures. 

Hundreds of Oklahomans are discovering that new FEMA flood plain maps have placed property they own in an area that would require them to purchase flood insurance.  Many of those new designations apparently were made improperly. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>184</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-09-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/03-09-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/03-09-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>693</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[For the first time in more than a year, state revenues for last month exceeded the official estimate.  However, in order to avoid increasing the10% budget cuts the state had to borrow nearly $85-million from cash reserves. 

The House has approved a bill that would make firearms, accessories and ammunition made and kept in the state, exempt from regulation by the federal government. 

A plan to bring grand prix auto racing to Oklahoma City has been approved by the city council.  A 1.9 mile course around the Bricktown Entertainment District is being planned for the summer of 2011. 

In-Depth tonight we talk with an official of the Commerce Department who oversees a little known nutrition program aimed at senior citizens. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>183</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-08-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_03-08-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_03-08-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>691</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The Director of the CIA talked with students at the University of Oklahoma today about the work of his agency and the major challenges to the nationÂ’s security. 

  The 10th U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals has rejected a suit from the Osage nation that claimed its reservation still exists and covers all of Osage County. 

With a deal in place to fund Senior Nutrition Centers after July 1st, we talk In-Depth tonight about what the impact has been on seniors across the state as many of them watched their nutrition centers shut down. 

The 1st Lady recently launched a nationwide program to get youngsters to lose weight and improve their physical condition.  The ONR visits an elementary school to check out the free breakfast to see just what youngsters eat at the start of their school day. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>182</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-05-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_03-05-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_03-05-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>689</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Professors, publishers and students got together today at Tulsa Community College to look for ways to reduce the cost of college textbooks. 

The recession is being blamed for layoffs of 56 employees at Comanche County Memorial Hospital in Lawton.  Those loosing their jobs include the hospitals chief operating officer. 

The national unemployment rate remained the same this month as last. Tonight we talk In-Depth with an expert on the job market about what is happening nationally and in Oklahoma to create new opportunities for employment. 

Looking back to help the state do better in the future. Oklahoma Horizon talks with Dr. Bob Blackburn. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>181</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-04-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_03-04-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_03-04-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>688</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[With little opposition, the state Senate has approved a bill allowing public schools to offer an elective course on the Bible. 
 
In the first round of national competition for a share of the Race to the Top funding, Oklahoma did not make the finalist list.  The Governor says the state will try again later this year. 

The Oklahoma House has approved a bill requiring mobile home parks to have a plan in place for residents to seek shelter during violent weather. 

School patrons in Skiatook, upset with their school board for not providing information on a purchasing scandal, have launched a petition drive for a grand jury investigation. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>180</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-03-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_03-03-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_03-03-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>687</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The battle over the 2010 budget continues in the state Senate.  Senate Republicans are expected to hold another vote today on bills that have to pass for the budget agreement between legislative leaders and the governor to be enacted.  

Skiatook School Superintendent Gary Johnson is still getting a paycheck but the school board suspended him following a closed door meeting that left patrons angry.  The board has yet to give taxpayers any explanation for how more than half a million dollars was wasted in a purchasing scandal.
 
A new museum is opening in Tulsa, to help preserve the history of the cityÂ’s art deco architecture. 

Graduates this year at the University of Oklahoma will be offered biodegradable graduation gowns made of wood fiber harvested from renewable managed forests.  The zippers are from recycled material and it all disintegrates in a landfill within a year. ]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>179</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-02-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_03-02-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_03-02-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>686</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Talks began last evening and continued today between Republican and Democratic leaders to try and end the budget standoff that began late in the day in the state Senate. So far no deals have been reached and furloughs and layoffs are just days away without the increased spending. 

We talk In-Depth tonight with an official of the Highway Patrol about what the stalled budget agreement would do for the agency if an agreement can be reached on additional spending for Senior Nutrition programs. 

The House has approved a bill to require women who want an abortion, to undergo an ultrasound before the procedure is done.  The bill is one of several individual measures that were originally part of a larger bill passed last year that was ruled unconstitutional 

City government and school bond elections are being held in several locations around the state.  Many school districts are depending on bonds to pay for building improvements and repairs during the ongoing budget cutbacks. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>178</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 03-01-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_03-01-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_03-01-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>685</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The U.S. Supreme Court has declined to hear an appeal of the 10 Commandments case from Haskell County.  That means the lower court ruling that the marker must be removed will stand. 

75 more state employees are now out of work with the closure of two state homes for the mentally disabled.  Facilities in Enid and Pauls Valley were shut down due to ongoing budget cuts. 

The House has approved a bill to create a voluntary program to register and inspect breeders of puppies and kittens. 

Over the weekend, a 4.1 magnitude earth quake shook the ground in Oklahoma.  It was the strongest quake to hit the state in over a decade.  Tonight we talk In-Depth with a seismologist about what is going on under ground. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>177</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 02-25-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_02-25-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_02-25-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>683</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The state Senate votes to move the embattled Medical Examiners office to new facilities on the campus of the University of Central Oklahoma. 

Senate President Pro Temp Glenn Coffee says he will change his no vote on a bill keeping the dates of birth of government employees secret.  He is also calling for balance on a bill to keep secret the financial records of the state Film Commission which gives tax rebates to movie makers. 

A report from the Rockefeller Institute shows Oklahoma government revenue dropped more during the final quarter of 2009 than any other state in the nation. 

An In-Depth report tonight on the presidentÂ’s Health Care Meeting and comments from Senator Tom Coburn that found wide ranging support. 

The Oklahoma House has approved a bill making it illegal for a woman to sell her eggs. The bill does not ban men from selling sperm. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>176</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 02-24-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_02-24-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_02-24-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>681</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The Oklahoma Senate is slated to debate resolutions that would remove the state from any national health care reform law and require the Attorney General to sue the federal government to block the reforms from going into effect. 

Long time Senate staffer, Charles Israel was found unconscious in a menÂ’s room at the state Capitol late Tuesday.  Later, he passed away at an Oklahoma City Hospital.  Israel suffered from muscular dystrophy. 
 
Five more public schools are under investigation by the state Auditor for how they have been spending money.  Few of those school officials have been willing to talk about the probe. 

In our Â“ItÂ’s your MoneyÂ” segment tonight, the ONR examines the practice of communities spending millions of dollars to keep a business from moving away.  Do the tax payer funded incentives pay off in the long run? 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>175</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 02-23-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_02-23-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_02-23-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>679</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The state Auditor says Skiatook Public Schools use of a middleman to buy janitorial supplies and security systems wasted more than half a million dollars. 

The state Health Department sponsored Child Abuse Prevention day at the state capitol. The Main reason, the make a point to lawmakers that budget cuts could eliminate key programs that help prevent abuse and neglect of children. 

A bill approved by the state Senate would allow the Oklahoma Municipal Power Authority to buy electricity that is generated by a nuclear power plant.  It would also allow the authority to become a partner in the construction of such a facility in Oklahoma. 

In-Depth, we talk with an expert on how credit histories are now impacting the search for jobs as well as buying anything on credit. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>174</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 02-22-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_02-22-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_02-22-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>678</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The state Tax Commissions semi-annual report shows 460 tax breaks are costing the state $5.5-billion a year.  The tax loss may be higher since not all tax exemptions are included in the figures. 
 
Hundreds of students from alternative schools worked the halls of the state legislature today, asking lawmakers to keep their funding intact.  
The Oklahoma House is going to hear a bill to exempt guns made and sold in Oklahoma from federal regulation. 
 
The number of fatal car crashes involving 16 and 17 year olds has dropped dramatically since 2000.  ThatÂ’s when the states graduated driverÂ’s license law took effect. 

New rules go into effect today for credit card holders and we talk In-Depth with an expert about what those rules mean to consumers. ]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>173</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 02-19-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_02-19-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_02-19-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>677</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[An Oklahoma County district court judge has thrown out another anti-abortion law for the same reason; lawmakers rolled more than one issue into the bill. 
 
Attorney General Drew Edmondson says any move by the Texas A.G. to get involved in the Tarrant County water lawsuit will be met with stiff opposition from the state of Oklahoma. 

Four Oklahoma lawmakers got a taste of classroom teaching today in Tulsa. Part of a project to show legislators what teachers face each day. 

Our Newsmaker interview tonight features the Oklahoma Health Care Authority and the impact of a budget deal to give the agency $33-million more to avoid further cuts to Medicaid. ]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>172</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 02-18-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_02-18-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_02-18-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>676</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The Governor and legislative leaders are back behind closed doors, trying to finish an agreement on how to get through the budget crisis for this fiscal year and next. 

Just three years old, the Gatorade plant in Pryor Oklahoma is closing down.  The company blames the economic downturn for the closing. 

While members of the House see the need for emergency funding for the embattled Medical Examiners office, Senate President Pro Temp Glenn Coffee disagrees.  He says fiscal responsibility is necessary first. 

We talk In-Depth tonight about a new way to renew or purchase a new license plate.  Do it On-Line. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>171</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 02-17-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_02-17-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_02-17-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>674</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[A Senate committee has voted to sell Compsource, the state owned issuer of Workers Compensation insurance to companies that cannot get the coverage elsewhere. 

The Oklahoma Policy Institute reports the state has more than 450 tax breaks that cost the state $5.6-billion in 2008. No one reviews the tax breaks to see if they are being abused. 

A group backing the use of medical marijuana worked the hallways of the state capitol today looking for support for such a measure.
 
The White House says stimulus money, among other things, saved 23,000 Oklahoma jobs including covering the costs of nearly 5,000 teachers over the last year. 
An In-Depth discussion with Tulsa Public Schools Superintendent on the impact of ongoing state budget cuts.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>170</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 02-16-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_02-16-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_02-16-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>673</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[A group of state legislators took a look today to the State Medical Examiners Office.  Results of their inspection tonight on the ONR. 

The state Equalization Board is told there will be slightly more money for lawmakers to spend next fiscal year but the state will still be more than a billion dollars short compared to this yearÂ’s budget. 

State Sen. Tom Adelson says he has found a way to bring in 100Â’s of millions of dollars to state government.  The senator wants new oversight of current tax breaks and elimination of those that donÂ’t produce results. 

The states prescription monitoring program is getting the credit for leading to the arrest of former OSU Basketball Coach Sean Sutton.  Tonight we talk live with the Director of the Narcotics bureau about that program. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>169</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 02-12-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_02-12-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_02-12-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>669</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[New figures from the Tax Commission indicate state government may have a little more money to work with this fiscal year and next.

The two sides of the debate over monuments to the 10 Commandments on public land from the University of Oklahoma Law School. 

Former OSU basketball coach Sean Sutton is in jail, accused of trying to illegally obtain painkillers.

OklahomaÂ’s high poverty rate gets some of the blame for childhood obesity because it limits access to fresh foods. 

TonightÂ’s Newsmaker Interview features the leadership of the Oklahoma House and Senate and the Governor, on the budget crisis and much more. 

]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>168</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 02-11-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_02-11-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_02-11-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>672</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[A Senate committee approves three bills that would further restrict access to abortions. 

Oklahoma doctors say plans to further reduce Medicaid reimbursements will force many doctors to leave the state and further restrict access to health care for the states most needy.
 
The House has approved a series of bills to add funding to education, health care, public safety and get the current fiscal year budget back in balance.  However, it offers far less funds from the rainy day fund than the Governor wants. 

Senate President Pro Tem Glenn Coffee says he is pleased that his proposals to opt out of any federal health care reform act are now headed for the Senate floor for a vote. 

We talk In-Depth with an Oklahoma doctor who has just returned from Haiti about the work that remains there in the recovery effort from a devastating earthquake. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>167</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 02-10-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_02-10-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_02-10-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>667</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[From the Capitol, we have a report on legislation that would allow teaching of the Bible in certain public school classes.  

Also, we will look at a bill that would require mobile home parks to have a plan for protecting tenants from tornadoes. 

We will have a story on a new program in Tulsa that is focused on reducing childhood obesity. 

In Depth, we talk about the impact of new credit card rules on Oklahomans. 
In our Preserving History franchise segment, we will have a story on people who are living and working in TulsaÂ’s Brady District. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>165</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 02-09-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_02-09-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_02-09-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>666</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[New state revenue numbers are out, showing a slight improvement for January. 
In Depth, we will talk to David Blatt of the Oklahoma Policy Institute about what the numbers mean for the state. 

Another proposal to eliminate the sales tax on groceries has passed out of a Senate committee and goes to the full Senate. 

In Preserving History, we will look at what is being done by Fort Gibson to find new sources of revenue. 

House and Senate Democrats suggest ending the legislative session early to save the state money. 

Professional hockey is returning to Oklahoma City, as an American Hockey League franchise is moving from Edmonton to the capitol city. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>164</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 02-08-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_02-08-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_02-08-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>664</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[A new term limit proposal for statewide elected officials has passed out of committee. 

A bill that would provide for performance pay for teachers has been approved by a house committee.
  
In Depth, we discuss the Tea Party movement with Al Gerhart, founder of the Oklahoma Constitutional Alliance. 

We learn more about a class on Confucius at Northeastern State University in Broken Arrow. 

We will have a follow-up on the robbery of the new grocery store in north Tulsa. 

In our Sunup franchise, we will have the latest on Â“no-tillÂ” farming. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>163</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 02-05-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_02-05-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_02-05-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>663</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The governor is now defending his plans to generate more than $660-million in new revenue to help balance next years budget.  He is calling on critics to come up with their own plan if they donÂ’t like his. 

 The Tulsa Convention center is filled with thousands of people getting free dental care.  Some people have waited in line for two days to get into the free dental clinic and more are already in line for tomorrow.  

School districts across the state are finding ways to make up the lost time in class because of the winter weather.  After missing another four because of the weather, Oklahoma City schools are closed again today this time for parent teacher meetings.  ThatÂ’s leading to some parents wondering why their children arenÂ’t in the classroom instead. 

Tulsa police will no longer respond to the scene of non-injury accidents.  But insurance agents are warning that will likely cause a spike in insurance rates for everyone because determining who was at fault in the accident will come down to one personÂ’s word against another. 

The battle over bringing part of the farm into the big city is being played out as the issue of raising chickens pits neighbor against neighbor with city hall in the middle. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>162</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 02-04-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_02-04-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_02-04-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>659</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The purported budget agreement reached by legislative leaders and the governor last month doesn't look like much of an agreement anymore.  Senate Pro tem Glenn Coffee and House Speaker Chris Benge have differing views on various components of the budget deal indicating there is not a lot of agreement on key issues of the budget blueprint for fiscal year 2011.   Senate staffers have been notified they may be placed on furlough for 12 days during the spring and summer.  Similar furloughs are not being planned for House staffers.   Facing major cutbacks in funding, some Oklahoma public schools are now looking at bond issues as a way to make up for lost funding from state government.   We take a tour of a school that is setting the trend for the future of education in Oklahoma.  Crescent High School is all digital which means textbooks have been virtually eliminated.   We talk In-Depth tonight with a top official of the Independent Petroleum Producers Association about what they see as the future for the states oil and natural gas industry.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>161</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 02-03-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_02-03-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_02-03-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>657</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[A senate subcommittee has endorsed a bill to allow high schools to begin offering an elective course in the study of the Bible.  Backers say the bill has guidelines to ensure the class focuses on the historical context of scripture and does not become a bible school class. 

Another senate bill winning initial approval would require new applicants for state welfare benefits to undergo a drug test first.  If they fail, benefits would be denied. 

Several Oklahoma Indian tribes recently received millions of dollars in stimulus funds to develop mass transit.  We take a look at how the Muscogee Creek nation is using its funds. 

A Duncan man found in possession of a grenade launcher that was allegedly stolen from a shipment headed for the troops in Iraq back in 2006, has been indicted by a federal grand jury.  29-year old Charles Alan Dyer is charged with unlawful possession of an unregistered destructive device. 

We talk In-Depth tonight with a State Wildlife Commission official about a number of new laws that purpose to consolidate various hunting and fishing licenses.  And about a bill to allow hunters to use silencers. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>160</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 02-02-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_02-02-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_02-02-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>651</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Rural lawmakers are lining up against a proposal in the governors 2011 budget that removes funding from the Rural Economic Action Plan or REAP.  The budget consolidates several state agencies and freezes or removes millions in tax breaks. 

The Corporation Commission joins the growing ranks of state agencies sending workers home without pay to meet budget cuts. 

Since Thursday, the secure juvenile facility in Manitou has been without power.  It also has now lost water supplies.  48 young people are housed at the facility. 

Work has begun in the Oklahoma House and Senate on the more than 2,000 bills lawmakers faces this session.  Right now all the work is focused in committee meetings. Today the Senate Judiciary Committee which takes up several proposed exemptions to the states Open Records Act. 

A dairy operation that bills itself as Â“All NaturalÂ” is featured in the ONR Living Well segment this evening.  
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>159</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 02-01-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_02-01-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_02-01-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>649</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The Governors last budget calls for elimination or freezing of millions of dollars in tax credits or tax breaks.  He also wants to consolidate numerous state agencies.  By spending nearly all of the Rainy Day fund he would keep budget cuts in 2011 to 7.5%. 

Legislative leaders broadly praised the Governors final State of the State speech.  Most were pleased with his overall tone of working together to keep the budget balanced. 

Tulsa firefighters agree to pay cuts to keep their jobs.  Tulsa police say no and lose more than 100 jobs. 

The latest economic indicators show OklahomaÂ’s economy is expanding.  The latest figures show the chance of a double dip recession has also gone down significantly. 

An old back injury has forced state Senator Mike Mazzei to take an indefinite leave of absence.  The 2008 injury left the senator with significant nerve damage.  
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>158</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 01-29-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_01-29-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_01-29-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>646</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The Governors last budget calls for elimination or freezing of millions of dollars in tax credits or tax breaks.  He also wants to consolidate numerous state agencies.  By spending nearly all of the Rainy Day fund he would keep budget cuts in 2011 to 7.5%.

Legislative leaders broadly praised the Governors final State of the State speech.  Most were pleased with his overall tone of working together to keep the budget balanced. 

CTulsa firefighters agree to pay cuts to keep their jobs.  Tulsa police say no and lose more than 100 jobs.

The latest economic indicators show OklahomaÂ’s economy is expanding.  The latest figures show the chance of a double dip recession has also gone down significantly. 

An old back injury has forced state Senator Mike Mazzei to take an indefinite leave of absence.  The 2008 injury left the senator with significant nerve damage.  
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>157</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 01-28-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_01-28-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_01-28-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>644</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[A major ice storm is again making its way across the state, downing power lines, causing major traffic problems and shutting down schools, government and businesses.  Damage estimates will begin once the storm is passed, right now the goal is to help people who have lost power. 

Tulsa police have overwhelmingly voted to reject the last contract concession offer from Mayor Dewey Bartlett.  The mayor says the vote means he will go forward with the layoffs of 155 officers. 

A $15,000 reward is now being offered for information leading to the arrest of a man suspected of killing his estranged wife and kidnapping her 7-year old daughter.  Aja Johnson was last seen last Saturday in Geronimo.  46-year old Lester Hobbs is the chief suspect. 

We talk with an expert at predicting just how much damage the state will suffer from the ice storm and how long the power may be out especially for rural Oklahomans. 

Reaction from the states congressional delegation to President ObamaÂ’s first State of the Union Speech. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>156</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 01-27-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_01-27-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_01-27-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>643</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[OklahomanÂ’s are stocking up on supplies and getting ready to deal with another major winter storm.  The latest tonight from ONR Meteorologist Ross Dixon. 
Southwest Airlines has cancelled all of its flights beginning after 7:30 am Thursday morning out of Oklahoma City and Tulsa because of the expected storm.
 
Just as another blast of winter weather moves in, the annual homeless count has begun in central Oklahoma. 

Oklahoma City Mayor Mick Cornett will be sitting with 1st Lady Michelle Obama during the State of the Union speech tonight.  The 1st Lady invited him to attend to highlight his weight loss program for Oklahoma City. 
 
We talk In-Depth tonight with the states top banking official about the proposed new rules the Obama administration wants to put in place for the nations banking system. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>155</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 01-26-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_01-26-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_01-26-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>642</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[  City, county and state governments are all gearing up for the response they anticipate will be needed to the next big snow storm, due to hit the state early Thursday.  That includes e tree trimming companies that are working extra to remove limbs near power lines. 

   Governor Henry says if the state had done what he wanted back in 2006, the Rainy Day fund would now have nearly a billion dollars.  He now wants to raise the cap on the fund so when contributions to the fund resume it can grow much higher. 

   State Sen. Randy Brogdon wants to remove the ability to raise tolls on turnpikes from the Turnpike Authority.  Brogdon, also a candidate for governor, also wants to restrict the authorityÂ’s ability to issue bonds. 

   Oklahoma continues to lead the nation in the percentage of women behind bars. A major gathering of civic and governmental leaders today again examines the problems and solutions to the female incarceration rate. 

  Be careful when you fill out your tax returns this year.  Almost hidden deep down the form is the line for the Making Work Pay tax credit.   Do it yourself filers have been missing the new line and not benefiting from the tax credit which is part of the Stimulus Act.   We talk with an IRS official about that issue and more as tax time has arrived. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>154</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 01-25-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_01-25-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_01-25-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>640</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Over the weekend the WomenÂ’s Resources Center in Norman held an auction and sold off the last of its office equipment and supplies and then closed.  Its one casualty in what those involved in helping people recover from domestic violence say, is likely a statewide trend if budget cuts become larger. 
 
 There is a tentative deal to avoid laying off Tulsa firefighters that is being voted on by Union members through Friday.  However, no new tentative deal has been reached with Tulsa police, instead a new offer is on the table but it still involves a 5.2% pay cut.  

One of OklahomaÂ’s major union leaders doesnÂ’t care for the new U.S. Supreme Court ruling that removes limits on corporate and labor union campaign donations.  Jimmy Curry heads the Oklahoma AFL-CIO and talks live tonight on the ONR on his view of the impact from the high courts decision. 

He may have missed the January 1st deadline but Governor Brad Henry says he hopes to find a new Chief Information Officer sometime next month.  244 people applied for the job and 55 met the minimum qualifications. 

About 100 jobs at Claremore Â–based Centrilift are being lost to Houston.  No further information was released on why the Baker-Hughes branch company is moving the jobs out of state. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>153</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 01-22-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_01-22-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_01-22-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>632</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Hundreds of Tulsa police, firefighters and non-uniformed employees lost their jobs today as city officials were unable to find common ground with labor unions on other plans to save money.  Mayor Bartlett also asked for the Police Chief Ron Palmer to resign. 

The state Ethics Commission is voting on new rules to get into compliance with a new ruling from the U.S. Supreme Court that allows corporations and labor unions to spend unlimited funds for or against political candidates. 

What can one person do?   For an elderly Mustang man, watching senior nutrition programs across the state being shut down due to budget cuts meant he had to do something to help.  The story of one manÂ’s effort to feed senior citizens. 

Oklahoma U.S. Senator Jim Inhofe has angered Muslim groups with comments he made during a meeting of the Armed Service Committee.  Inhofe endorsed racial and ethic profiling and said all terrorists, with a few exceptions, are Muslims. 

Where the Jobs are.  The special segment from Horizon features the effort to upgrade the states work force to be more competitive in the global market place. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>152</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 01-21-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_01-21-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_01-21-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>624</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[<p>19 employees of the Board of Career and Technology Education have resigned as part of a voluntary separation plan because of ongoing state budget cuts.  The board was hoping more than 30 workers would take the deal.   Senate GOP leaders have rolled out the second half of their agenda for the new session. Public Safety and transportation funding are top priorities plus harsher penalties for human trafficking and making it easier to get a gun license.    State employees are now banned from sending text messages while driving.  The governor signed an executive order to that effect this morning.   Mobile home park owners donÂ’t care for a proposed new law that would require evacuation plans or storm shelters in their parks.  Many are concerned about the costs involved. The bills author says he is revamping his measure to meet their concerns.   We talk In-Depth tonight with a political science professor on the implications of a new U.S. Supreme Court ruling that allows corporations and unions to spend as much money as they want endorsing or opposing a specific candidate</p>]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>151</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 01-20-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle>ONR 01-20-10</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_01-20-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_01-19-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>622</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[<p>Oklahoma News Report</p>]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>150</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 01-19-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_01-19-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_01-19-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>621</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[<p>Altus Air Force personnel are gearing up for deployment to Haiti.  The crews of the 58th Airlift Squadron began preparing two C-17 Globemaster III aircraft over the weekend.   State Rep. David Dank has a message for House Speaker Chris Benge: support my property tax cap or step down.  Benge is not expected to change his opinion on the measure or step down.  Dank wants property tax increases capped at three percent, per year.   How much would it cost, who would do it and how do you make sure they know what they're doing?  All questions the Oklahoma News Report will attempt to get answers for concerning a bill that would require couples to attend pre-marital counseling before being allowed to get a marriage license.  It’s one of thousands of new bills lawmakers will begin work on in less than two weeks.   Tonight an interview with the governor’s Innovation director for Public Education, on the state’s application for Race to the Top funds.   Another Oklahoma museum is struggling to make it through budget cuts and reduced tourism.  Officials of the Will Rogers Museum in Claremore are looking for ways to cope with the loss of funds and keep the facility operating.   It’s that time of year and free filing is available to Oklahomans to take care of their tax returns. We talk with the IRS about how to do it tonight on the ONR.</p>]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>149</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 01-15-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_01-15-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_01-15-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>619</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[<p>The earthquake swarm that has been shaking central Oklahoma got more intense today as another quake hit the Jones area and hit 4.0.  It was felt all across Oklahoma and parts of Logan and Lincoln counties.   Organizations, charities, university students and others across the state are launching fund drives to raise money to aid in relief efforts in Haiti.   The latest state agency to layoff employees is the Indigent Defense System.  8 employees are being let go as the agency that provides defense attorneys to defendants unable to pay for a private attorney, copes with a $1.8-million budget cut.   District Attorney's statewide are now looking at furloughs as a way to cope with the ongoing budget crisis.  So far only one D.A. has decided to furlough employees but several are still studying such a plan and most are more concerned about the budget they will face for fiscal year 2011 which begins this July.   January is mentoring month.  Tonight we profile a man who began mentoring school kids with his wife.  After she passed away, mentoring children is now his primary activity.</p>]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>148</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 01-14-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_01-14-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_01-14-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>618</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>147</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 1-13-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_1-13-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_1-13-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>616</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>146</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 01-12-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_1-12-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_1-12-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>614</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[<p>Another state revenue report is due out this afternoon.  State agencies are on the second month of a 10-percent across the board cutback.   Senate Republicans unveil,  half of their agenda for the upcoming legislative session.  The GOP members of the senate want to cap property taxes at 3% a year and are opposed to any new taxes.    The state Fire Marshal has begun a furlough plan to deal with ongoing budget cuts.  The days off work without pay will impact only the administrative staff.   The state schools for the blind and deaf are being impacted by state budget cuts more than other departments in the state Department of Rehabilitation Services.  The schools operate just off of state funds and donations.  Agency officials say they are doing all they can to keep both schools accredited and intact.   For the first time since the 2003 budget crisis, the average amount of money spent for each student in Oklahoma public schools is going down. The mid-year allocations were sent out to the school districts this week.   The Hitachi Computer Products plant in Norman is doubling in size with the addition of a new distribution center.  That will mean about 75 new jobs.</p>]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>145</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 01-11-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_01-11-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_01-11-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>611</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[A regional economist with the Federal Reserve Board says Oklahoma is showing the early signs of economic recovery.  However, Chad Wilkerson says the states full recovery is precarious due to ever changing energy prices. 

The latest service to be slashed due to ongoing revenue failures in state government will impact victims of domestic abuse. The cuts include counseling and prevention services. Staff and benefits are also being cut to keep shelters for battered women in operation. 

Thursday is the deadline for lawmakers to pre-file bills for the new legislative session.  Among the hundreds of new laws being introduced is a bill from Senator Steve Russell to allow hunters to use silencers on their weapons. 

The aftermath of frigid arctic air is broken water mains.  While there is no official count, between Tulsa and Oklahoma City there may be 30 repair jobs or more waiting for crews to fix. 

The Tulsa trucking company that closed its doors, stranding hundreds of drivers across the nation three days before Christmas, is now filing for bankruptcy.  Over the weekend Arrow Trucking company filed the paperwork to seek liquidation.    
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>144</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 01-08-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_1-08-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_1-11-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>610</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[A regional economist with the Federal Reserve Board says Oklahoma is showing the early signs of economic recovery.  However, Chad Wilkerson says the states full recovery is precarious due to ever changing energy prices. The latest service to be slashed due to ongoing revenue failures in state government will impact victims of domestic abuse. The cuts include counseling and prevention services. Staff and benefits are also being cut to keep shelters for battered women in operation. Thursday is the deadline for lawmakers to pre-file bills for the new legislative session.  Among the hundreds of new laws being introduced is a bill from Senator Steve Russell to allow hunters to use silencers on their weapons. The aftermath of frigid arctic air is broken water mains.  While there is no official count, between Tulsa and Oklahoma City there may be 30 repair jobs or more waiting for crews to fix. The Tulsa trucking company that closed its doors, stranding hundreds of drivers across the nation three days before Christmas, is now filing for bankruptcy.  Over the weekend Arrow Trucking company filed the paperwork to seek liquidation.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>143</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 01-07-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_01-07-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_01-07-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>607</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>142</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 01-06-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_1-6-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_1-6-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>606</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>141</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 1-5-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_1-5-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_1-5-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>603</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[With the state ranked number 6 in the nation for the number of teen pregnancies, a program at an Oklahoma City middle school is showing promise in lowering the rate of children having children.  Teen Em Power is getting the credit for cutting the number of pregnant children at Taft Middle School to zero from six the semester before.  The program is funded through donations. 

An Oklahoman is among three Ft. Carson soldiers who were killed in Afghanistan in an attack by insurgents.  19-year old Private John P. Dion of Shattuck died Sunday from wounds he suffered when his unit was hit by small arms fire and improvised explosives. 

About two dozen schools in northeastern Oklahoma are still closed because of icy roads left over from recent winter storms.  While primary roads in the area have been cleared rural roads have not. 

House Speaker Chris Benge has cancelled any pre-session meetings of legislative committees to try and save money.  Lawmakers go back to work February 2nd and in past years committees meet to get ready for the session.  No pre-session meetings may save up to $20,000. 

The I.R.S. has decided to begin regulating tax preparers, to end abuses and errors in tax returns.  We talk with a CPA about what the new rules will mean for consumers. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>140</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 1-4-10</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_1-4-10.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_1-4-10.jpg</image>
			<identifier>602</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[With the state ranked number 6 in the nation for the number of teen pregnancies, a program at an Oklahoma City middle school is showing promise in lowering the rate of children having children.  Teen Em Power is getting the credit for cutting the number of pregnant children at Taft Middle School to zero from six the semester before.  The program is funded through donations.
 
An Oklahoman is among three Ft. Carson soldiers who were killed in Afghanistan in an attack by insurgents.  19-year old Private John P. Dion of Shattuck died Sunday from wounds he suffered when his unit was hit by small arms fire and improvised explosives. 

About two dozen schools in northeastern Oklahoma are still closed because of icy roads left over from recent winter storms.  While primary roads in the area have been cleared rural roads have not. 

House Speaker Chris Benge has cancelled any pre-session meetings of legislative committees to try and save money.  Lawmakers go back to work February 2nd and in past years committees meet to get ready for the session.  No pre-session meetings may save up to $20,000. 

The I.R.S. has decided to begin regulating tax preparers, to end abuses and errors in tax returns.  We talk with a CPA about what the new rules will mean for consumers. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>139</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 12-30-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_12-30-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_12-30-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>601</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>138</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 12-29-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_12-29-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_12-29-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>600</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>137</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 12-28-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_12-28-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_12-28-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>599</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>136</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 12-23-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_12-23-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_12-23-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>598</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>135</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 12-22-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_12-22-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_12-22-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>597</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>134</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 12-21-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_12-21-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_12-21-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>596</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>133</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 12-18-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_12-18-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_12-18-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>595</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[State Treasurer Scott Meacham briefs the media today on what the state budget looks like for the rest of the fiscal year and a look into projections for the 2011 fiscal year.  The numbers are based on estimates from the state Tax Commission which go before the state equalization board on Monday. 

Tulsa Police and Fire fighters are now expected to loose more than 100 employees per department unless there is a major increase in sales tax income for the city of Tulsa.  A final decision on the cuts is expected by mid-January.
  
A late afternoon hearing is scheduled in Oklahoma County District Court, to decide if an order keeping the states new abortion law from going into effect will stay in place.  Judge Daniel Owens will also hear arguments from the state to dismiss the case against the law and allow it to go into effect. 

The Corporation Commission has put on hold a decision on a new area code for the region now covered by 918.  Numbers for the current 918 area are expected to run out in a couple of years. 

8 more Oklahoma communities are now viewing OETA in digital mode.  Conversions of the networks low power transmitters continues into next week with all conversions expected to be complete by the first of the year. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>132</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 12-17-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_12-17-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_12-17-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>594</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[ The Director of the Department of Corrections told us that additional state budget cuts are putting public safety at risk in the state prison system.   

 In Depth, we talk to David Blatt of the Oklahoma Policy Institute about the current state budget crisis.  

 Cathy Tatom had a story on extreme geothermal drilling technology that will allow wells to be drilled up to 30,000 feet under the surface to provide geothermal power. 

 Students at two middle schools in Tulsa are learning about our democratic way of life by participating in the History Bowl. Angela Rosecrans had the story.   

]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>131</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Oklahoma News Report</title>
			<ov:subtitle>12-16-09</ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_12-16-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_12-16-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>591</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>130</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 12-15-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_12-15-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_12-15-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>589</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>129</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 12-14-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_12-14-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_12-14-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>588</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The Corporation Commission approves a rate hike for Oklahoma Natural Gas Company.  The increase is part of a deal worked out between the utility, the attorney generals office and large industrial users.  ONG says it needs more money because of infrastructure costs. 

Oral Roberts is reported to be in stable condition at a California hospital after a fall over the weekend.  The televangelist is being treated for broken bones and pneumonia. 

State Senator Constance Johnson is calling for elimination of the death penalty in Oklahoma.  

A state lawmaker says he will introduce a bill next year, to lower the monthly allotment lawmakers receive for health care insurance to match that of education employees.  Lawmakers currently receive $608 a month for themselves, $609 dollars a month for their spouse and 75% of that for dependants. 

Today OETA begins the switch over of its low power transmitter sites from analog to digital.  We follow the process and talk with Deputy Director Mark Norman about what this means for viewers across the state. 
 

]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>128</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 12-011-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_12-11-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_12-11-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>587</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Economists with a national legislative group are predicting state budgets will take up to another two years to recover from the recession.  The latest revenue collections for state government are due out next week, with the latest budget projections due out the week after that. 

The state Ethics Commission is being urged to begin charging fines for politicians who fail to meet deadlines for filing campaign reports.  Those fines can go as high as $1,000 a day. Ethics Commission officials have told a House Subcommittee that it would need to hire at least one additional employee to begin processing the fines. 

One new death is being reported in the state because of H1N1 Flu.  A Garfield county man died last week from the virus.  The death of a Kiowa County man several weeks ago has not yet been confirmed as swine flu related. 

11 Oklahoma Indian tribes are receiving millions of dollars in federal funding to improve mass transit systems on Indian lands.  The funding is split between regular federal funding and money from the Stimulus Act. 

We talk with an expert about the pitfalls of early retirement as it pertains to Social Security benefits.  As the life span of Americans increases, more workers are staying on the job longer and that could mean a bigger monthly check once retirement time does arrive.]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>127</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 12-10-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_12-10-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_12-10-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>583</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>126</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 12-09-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_12-09-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_12-09-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>582</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>125</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 12-08-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_12-08-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_12-08-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>580</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>124</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 12-07-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_12-07-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_12-07-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>579</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[ On the eve of a vote by Oklahoma City residents on the MAPS 3 proposal, more organized opposition has appeared.  A group calling itself Advocates for Justice added its voice to that of police and fire unions who oppose the sales tax vote.  

The OSBI says it has reached a dead end in its investigation into the murder of Pastor Carol Daniels in her Anadarko church. The Caddo County D.A. says he is dismayed by the lack of progress.  

More than 100 Oklahomans are now looking for real health care insurance after discovering the company they were paying premiums to was instead ripping them off.  American Trade Association allegedly sold fake health insurance plans and to continue the scam continually changed its name with new fake contact information.  People in at least 20 states were victims with at least $14-million in premiums paid to the company. 

More than 100 people are now out of a job and their last paychecks after a Tulsa marketing firm abruptly closed down.  Automated Research and Marketing had been in business for nine years. 

Sneezy the elephant is one potent guy.  The Oklahoma City Zoo shipped Sneezy to Tulsa to try and start a love affair of sorts with Asha and now word comes that on the first attempt things went according to plan and now the Tulsa Zoo elephant is expecting.  She is expected to deliver the new arrival in May of 2011. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>123</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 12-04-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_12-04-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_12-04-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>578</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The Office of Juvenile Affairs has shut down one facility, ended programs and put employees on one day a month furloughs to keep up with ongoing state budget cuts.  OJA officials have told lawmakers if the budget cuts get bigger, they will have to close secure lockups for juvenile offenders. 

For the first time since it began in 1992, the Oklahoma Higher Learning Access Program has more than 10,000 students enrolled from a single graduating class.  Recent changes to the system were designed to expand eligibility to the program. 

Tonight we take a tour of the newly opened Oklahoma Sports Hall of Fame and Jim Thorpe Museum.  The facility is home to three unique exhibits that include the multitude of famous Oklahoma sports figures as well has providing a home for Jim Thorpe memorabilia. 

Living in north Tulsa has meant driving for many miles to find a grocery store.  That is about to change as the first food store in many years is opening its doors as part of a larger economic development project for the area.  Community leaders say race issues were largely behind the lack of such services in the past. 

Tonight Captain Kirk will get onboard a reining horse to take part in the Performance Horses Celebrity Slide for the Make-A-Wish foundation of Oklahoma.  William Shatner along with Lyle Lovett and other celebrities are giving their time to raise funds for a program that gives a final wish to a child with a terminal illness. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>122</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 12-03-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_12-03-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_12-03-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>575</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>121</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 12-02-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_12-02-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_12-02-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>573</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>120</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 12-01-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_12-01-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_12-01-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>571</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The state Corrections Board is telling lawmakers it is time to look at old solutions to deal with a current crisis.  Facing more than $22-million in cutbacks this fiscal year, the Corrections Department is seeing a growing backlog of prisoners waiting for a bed in a prison system that is at capacity.  The suggestions include putting the CAP law back in place to let non-violent offenders out of prison early.

Researchers at the O.U. Health Sciences Center have discovered a synthetic compound that may have the potential to one day be used as a pill to prevent cancer.  Lab tests show the compound kills 12 different kinds of cancer.  Several more rounds of trials for the compound mean at least five years before it could be used as a treatment for cancer patients. 

House sub-committees begin a new round of hearings on the ailing state budget. Facing at least a billion dollar shortfall, House leaders are urging agencies to not show up with just negative news about the impact of cutbacks but instead find positive ways to make their operations more efficient. 

Tonight part one of our series, Meth Madness tells the story of two very different women who shared the same problem, methamphetamine addiction.  The ONR investigation finds that at any given time there are up to 900 people on waiting lists to get into a treatment facility.  Most never make it to treatment. 

A pair of Oklahoma universities is joining forces to launch a new program aimed at addressing a shortage of physicians in the state.  O.U. and T.U. will collaboration a new four year community medical education program.   

]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>119</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 11-30-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_11-30-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_11-30-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>570</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>118</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 11-25-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_11-25-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_11-25-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>569</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>117</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 11-24-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_11-24-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_11-24-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>568</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>116</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 11-23-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_11-23-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_11-23-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>567</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The holiday shopping season is about to hit high gear, just as credit card companies are scrambling to raise interest rates and fees.  We talk with an expert about using the credit card this Christmas and the financial hang-over that might cause. 

The Salvation Army has officially launched its annual Angel Tree campaign to provide holiday gifts for needy children and senior citizens.  This year the Army hopes to spread Christmas cheer to more than 18-hundred families. 

Cities across the state are facing falling income from sales taxes and the latest to make dramatic cuts to deal with the shortfall is the city of Bartlesville.  Dealing with an 11% drop in income the city is looking at furloughs and other cutbacks. 

The deer hunting season for guns began over the weekend.  We take a look at how the season is shaping up and the impact of deer season on the states economy. 

A new grain is being test grown in Oklahoma.  The high protein, gluten free grain may develop into a profitable market for smaller producers. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>115</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 11-20-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_11-20-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_11-20-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>566</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>114</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 11-19-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_11-19-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_11-19-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>565</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>113</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 11-17-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_11-17-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_11-17-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>561</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[OSU Economists are out with their expectations for the states economy.  The experts say Oklahoma should not expect to see benefits from a recovery until at least 2012.  Despite higher oil and natural gas prices, unemployment is expected to remain high until then. 

The state School Board is asking the governor to immediately access the Rainy Day Fund to cover the ongoing shortfall for state schools.  The board also approved a funding request for the next fiscal year that is more than $225-million dollars above their current budget.
 
Oklahoma is now receiving a failing grade in the annual March of Dimes Premature Birth Report Card. One in eight babies in the state is born prematurely.  

State Health officials have announced the swine flu vaccine is now available to all Oklahomans.  90,000 doses of the vaccine are expected in the state this week. 


]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>112</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 11-16-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_11-16-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_11-16-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>560</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>111</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 11-13-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_11-13-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_11-13-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>559</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>110</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 11-12-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_11-12-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_11-12-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>549</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>109</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 11-09-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_11-06-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_11-06-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>545</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Edmond city officials are feeling unfairly treated, because their senior nutrition center was closed.  The Mayor says their center feed 65 people every day which is a large site and it was closed because of the perception that Edmond is a wealthy city that can afford to cover the cost of the feeding program. 

A new poll of Oklahomans shows 83% support development of wind power and are willing to pay more for it.  They also favor mandates that require more wind power production.  The poll was done as a way to influence policy on wind energy in the months ahead. 

Relatives of Jim Thorpe are going to court to try and have his body reburied in Oklahoma.  His remains are currently interred in Jim Thorpe Pennsylvania in a deal that was put together by his widow. 

The Oklahoma City Animal Shelter has set a record for, Adoptions.  Last month 777 animals were adopted out to new homes.  The shelter has a special offer right now for anyone looking to adopt a pet. 

We talk In-Depth with the Chairman of the Political Science Department at OCU about the 20th anniversary of the fall of the Berlin Wall and what if any lasting impact that event has on the world. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>108</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 11-09-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/11-09-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/11-09-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>546</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Edmond city officials are feeling unfairly treated, because their senior nutrition center was closed.  The Mayor says their center feed 65 people every day which is a large site and it was closed because of the perception that Edmond is a wealthy city that can afford to cover the cost of the feeding program. 

A new poll of Oklahomans shows 83% support development of wind power and are willing to pay more for it.  They also favor mandates that require more wind power production.  The poll was done as a way to influence policy on wind energy in the months ahead. 

Relatives of Jim Thorpe are going to court to try and have his body reburied in Oklahoma.  His remains are currently interred in Jim Thorpe Pennsylvania in a deal that was put together by his widow. 

The Oklahoma City Animal Shelter has set a record for, Adoptions.  Last month 777 animals were adopted out to new homes.  The shelter has a special offer right now for anyone looking to adopt a pet. 

We talk In-Depth with the Chairman of the Political Science Department at OCU about the 20th anniversary of the fall of the Berlin Wall and what if any lasting impact that event has on the world. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>107</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 11-06-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_11-06-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_11-06-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>537</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>106</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 11-05-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_11-05-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_11-05-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>534</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[For the first time in nearly three decades, cameras will be allowed into an Oklahoma courtroom to cover an entire 1st degree murder trial.  An Oklahoma County Judge made the ruling today in the case of Jerome Ersland, a pharmacist who shot and killed a 16-year old would be armed robber. The Oklahoma News Report is part of the media pool that will be providing coverage of the trail.
 
Budget cuts are coming to an Oklahoma institution of higher learning.  USAO in Chickasha is cutting salaries, furloughing workers during the holidays and ending annuity payments to try and balance their budget. 

The I.R.S. is looking for more than 11-hundred Oklahomans who are due refunds but the checks were returned as undeliverable.  The checks total more than a million dollars. 

 As an Enid couple was driving home from church along a rural road outside of town, they encountered a site that truly caught them off guard.  Standing in the roadway was an elephant.  The car and the elephant did collide causing damage to the vehicle and breaking one of the elephants tusks and injuring a leg.  The injuries were not believed serious. The mammoth escaped from a nearby Circus company.   
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>105</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 11-04-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_11-04-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_11-04-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>533</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>104</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 11-03-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_11-03-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_11-03-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>532</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>103</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 11-02-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_11-02-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_11-02-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>530</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>102</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 10-30-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_10-30-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_10-30-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>527</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>101</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 10-29-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_10-29-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_10-29-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>520</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[County Commissioners across the state are approving a resolution that calls on the legislature to act quickly to replace the $7.4 million dollars that was cut by DHS from the Senior Nutrition Program.  Meanwhile, county officials are looking for ways to keep meals going to elderly residents while numerous centers and kitchens are being forced to close.
 
People lined up in the rain for blocks at the Tulsa Salvation Army offices today.  It was the opening of the sign-up period for people needing help over the holidays. 

Memorial services were held today for an Oklahoma City homeless veteran with full military honors thanks to a special program that steps in to provide services when no one claims the body of a veteran who has passed away.  
 
A government study on state-by-state differences in sleeplessness puts Oklahoma near the top of the list for people suffering from lack of sleep.  
Experts believe sleep-deprived people are more inclined to eat more fatty foods, plus they suffer from financial stress and odd-hour work shifts. 

We talk with the Tax Man about those tax credits for homeowners who make their houses more energy efficient by purchasing more energy efficient appliances. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>100</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 10-28-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_10-28-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_10-28-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>516</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[  PRESIDENT OBAMA NAMES O.U. PRESIDENT DAVID BOREN TO CO-CHAIR HIS INTELLIGENCE ADVISORY BOARD.
 
  A PAIR OF OKLAHOMA HOSPITALS ARE TAKING PART IN AN EXPERIMENT TO TRY A NEW WAY OF BILLING MEDICARE FOR HEALTH CARE SERVICES. 

  OKLAHOMA SENATOR TOM COBURN SLAMS HEALTH CARE REFORM AND GETS SLAMMED IN RETURN BY A FELLOW LAWMAKER. 

  WE GET A TOUR FROM AN EXPERT ON OKLAHOMA MYSTERIES, OF ONE OKLAHOMA COMMUNITY FILLED WITH MYSTERY&#039;S. 

 

]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>99</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 10-27-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_10-27-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_10-27-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>514</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>98</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 10-26-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_10-26-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_10-26-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>512</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>97</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 10-23-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_10-23-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_10-23-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>511</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>96</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 10-22-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_10-22-01.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_10-22-01.jpg</image>
			<identifier>510</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>95</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 10-21-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_10-21-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_10-21-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>505</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>94</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 10-20-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_10-20-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_10-20-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>504</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>93</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 10-19-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_10-19-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_10-19-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>502</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>92</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 10-16-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_10-16-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_10-16-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>501</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[ THE CITY OF BLACKWELL IS GOING TO COURT OVER THE MESS LEFT BEHIND BY A LEAD AND CADMIUM SMELTING OPERATION THAT SHUT DOWN IN 19-74. THE LAWSUIT CLAIMS THE SMELTER OPERATIONS LEFT BEHIND POLLUTANTS ON, BEYOND AND BENEATH THE PROPERTY WHERE THE SMELTER USED TO STAND.

 STATE HEALTH OFFICIALS ARE EXPECTING AN ADDITIONAL 65-THOUSAND-900 DOSES OF SWINE FLU VACCINE BY NEXT WEEK. LOCAL COUNTY HEALTH DEPARTMENTS WILL TARGET THE VACCINE TO SCHOOL CHILDREN AT LOCATIONS WHERE FLU ABSENTEEISM IS HIGH.

  THE ARCHITECT OF THE STATE CAPITOL IS RECOMMENDING THAT A 10 COMMANDMENTS MONUMENT BE PLACED ON THE NORTH SIDE OF THE BUILDING.  THE NORTH GROUNDS WERE ORIGINALLY DESIGNATED FOR MONUMENTS AND  HAS WALKWAYS NEAR WHERE THE MONUMENT COULD BE PLACED.BUT THE SOUTH SIDE OF THE CAPITOL IS CONSIDERED THE MAIN ENTRANCE TO THE BUILDING.A FINAL DECISION WILL BE MADE IN DECEMBER.  
 ]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>91</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 10-15-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_10-15-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_10-15-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>500</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>90</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 10-14-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_10-14-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_10-14-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>498</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>89</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 10-13-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_10-13-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_10-13-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>496</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>88</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 10-12-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_10-12-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_10-12-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>495</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>87</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 10-09-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_10-09-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_10-09-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>494</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[  Oklahoma is now setting a new record every day for the number of people receiving food stamps.  On average 500 new people are added to the food stamp rolls every day in Oklahoma.

  There&#039;s a rush of new home buyers in Oklahoma.  The $8,000 tax break for 1st time home buyers is driving the new business.  The deadline to buy a home and receive the tax credit is the end of December. 

  44,000 new doses of swine flu vaccine will arrive in Oklahoma in the next few days.  The vaccines will be in mist and injectable form.

  Health Departments across the state are already running out of the vaccine for this years regular strain of influenza.  ]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>86</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 10-8-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_10-8-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_10-8-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>492</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[According to a study by the Commonwealth Fund, Oklahoma ranks last among the states for health care access, cost and health outcomes.  The only areas of improvement found in the study for Oklahoma involved health care insurance and access for children. 

The death of a Lawton man is now being attributed to the H1N1 flu virus.  The death brings to at least six the number of Oklahomans who have died after contracting the flu virus. 

Another casualty of ongoing budget cuts in state government.  The Office of Juvenile Affairs is canceling a contract with a Pryor company that provides rehabilitative services for juvenile offenders.  A juvenile judge says the cut is a devastating loss. 

Past efforts to outlaw cell phone and text messaging while driving have failed in the state legislature.  But a legislative committee is examining the issue again and expects to be more successful in limiting such practices in the next session. 

Tonight we go In-Depth with Stateline.  A preview of the new documentary on the history of the Ku Klux Klan in Oklahoma and a live interview with producer Robert Burch on the past and present activities of the Klan in Oklahoma. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>85</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 10-7-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_10-7-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_10-7-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>489</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>84</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 10-05-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_10-05-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_10-05-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>484</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>83</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 10-02-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_10-2-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_10-2-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>481</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>82</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 10-01-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_10-1-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_10-1-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>480</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[The Oklahoma Department of Human Services has decided to cut nearly 30% of the state&#039;s nutrition program budget prompting a state lawmaker to call for a special legislative session.  Senator Kenneth Corn says the move will close senior nutrition centers statewide and imperil the lives of thousands of senior citizens. 

A group of state legislators is considering making Oklahoma&#039;s criminal code more user friendly. State Rep. Mark McCullough, (R) Sapulpa, says criminal law needs to be streamlined and centralized to make it easier for attorneys, judges, police and the public to understand. Critics say gutting existing statutes could have the unintended effect of loss of case law. 

President Obama has nominated Sandford Coats to be the new U.S. attorney for the Western District of Oklahoma. Coats has been assistant U.S. attorney since 2004. 

Congress&#039; failure to pass agency budget bills could cause problems for road and bridge projects in Oklahoma. The state is expecting $40 million in reimbursement, but there is no money in the Federal Highway Trust Fund to pay the state back. 

The first swine flu vaccine could arrive in Oklahoma early next week, but supply will be very limited. Only about 21,000 doses of flu mist inhaled inoculations are being made available for use by healthy people. The State Health Department is working on a plan to determine who will get them. 
New efforts are underway to ban text messaging while driving in Oklahoma. Currently 20 states and the District of Columbia prohibit the practice.   
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>81</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 9-30-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_9-30-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_9-30-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>478</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[A marine, U.S. Senator, Oklahoma Governor and a true statesman.  Henry Bellmon has died from complications from Parkinson&#039;s disease.  All state flags are now at half staff.  Expanded coverage tonight on the ONR. 

A lawsuit has been filed against a new bill that goes into effect November 1st that places new reporting requirements on abortion doctors.  The bill also does several other things which are the basis of the suit that cites a constitutional provision that all bills cover one subject at a time. 

According to new Census Bureau figures, nearly 25% of Oklahoma families with children under age 18 are receiving some sort of government assistance.  Many are on food stamps. 

O G & E has made a deal for two new wind farms in Northwest Oklahoma.  The public utility already has two wind generating farms in operation with a third expected to come on line by the end of the year.  The new facilities should be producing electricity by the end of 2010. 

And a new segment begins tonight on the ONR.  Living Well features an Oklahoma elementary school that improves the mind and the body. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>80</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 9-25-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_9-25-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_9-25-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>475</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Danny Rennels, former head of the Secondary Schools Activities Association pleads guilty to embezzlement charges.  No prison time ordered instead more than $421,000 in restitution must be paid within a month.  Relatives are paying the bill for Rennels who took the money to cover gambling debts. 

The 45th Infantry Museum unveils a new statue.  It honors the life and service of Lieutenant Col. Ernest Childers who is a Medal of Honor recipient from World War II. 

Students at McAlester High School have a new tool to explore the cosmos.  Their own observatory which includes a computer-controlled 12-inch telescope.  It took two years of effort by science teacher Phillip Scott to complete the project. 

Tonight we go In-Depth with debate from the floor of the U.S. Senate.  Oklahoma Senator Tom Coburn tried to block spending any more money to acquire new federal lands until the nation takes care of maintenance at existing national parks. 

And in conjunction with the new Ken Burns documentary on the National Parks, we get a first look at a film that highlights one of Oklahoma&#039;s three national parks, the Chickasaw National Recreation Area. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>79</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 9-28-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_9-28-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_9-28-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>476</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[As the number of Oklahoma child abuse cases continue to increase, the state is reassessing the policies and practices it has followed to determine when children should be removed from their parents.  So far changes made to the system are showing a reduced number of repeat abuse cases. 
 
Emergency managers from across the state are meeting in Tulsa this week, for discussions on just how prepared the state is to deal with emergencies caused by mother-nature or man-made.  Plans are also being reviewed on how the state can help people along the gulf coast as hurricane season reaches its height. 
 
The states first bear hunting season opens this week.  Archery and muzzle-loader season begins Thursday in four southeastern counties.  The limit for the season is 20 bears.  There are an estimated 500 black bears statewide. 
 
O.U. head coach Bob Stoops says he doesn&#039;t know if Heisman Trophy winning quarterback Sam Bradford will be well enough to play in this weekend&#039;s game against Miami.  Coach Stoops says he will make an announcement before game time. 
 
Tonight we talk one-on-one with Cherie Blair, wife of former British Prime Minister Tony Blair.  She was in Oklahoma City last week to talk about one of her major projects, the U.N. Convention on the Rights of the Child. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>78</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 9-29-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_9-28-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_9-28-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>477</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[A marine, U.S. Senator, Oklahoma Governor and a true statesman.  Henry Bellmon has died from complications from Parkinson&#039;s disease.  All state flags are now at half staff.  Expanded coverage tonight on the ONR. 

A lawsuit has been filed against a new bill that goes into effect November 1st that places new reporting requirements on abortion doctors.  The bill also does several other things which are the basis of the suit that cites a constitutional provision that all bills cover one subject at a time. 

According to new Census Bureau figures, nearly 25% of Oklahoma families with children under age 18 are receiving some sort of government assistance.  Many are on food stamps. 

O G & E has made a deal for two new wind farms in Northwest Oklahoma.  The public utility already has two wind generating farms in operation with a third expected to come on line by the end of the year.  The new facilities should be producing electricity by the end of 2010. 

And a new segment begins tonight on the ONR.  Living Well features an Oklahoma elementary school that improves the mind and the body. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>77</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 9-24-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_9-24--09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_9-24--09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>473</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Swine flu has claimed another life in Oklahoma.  State Health officials will say only that the victim was a teenager in Cleveland County who had underlying health problems.  67 Oklahomans have been hospitalized with the H1N1 flu strain with most of those in just the last week.
 
Opening statements took all day as the long awaited Oklahoma lawsuit against the Arkansas poultry industry is now underway in Tulsa Federal Court.  The state argues the poultry industry has knowingly been polluting a million acre river valley for decades.  

State Rep. Ryan Kiesel says he will introduce a bill that puts a five cent deposit on all beverage containers, including glass, aluminum and plastic.  He says it will put extra cash in state coffers and reduce litter. 

A decision by the State Tax Commission to remove certain electric vehicles from a 1995 tax credit law has now produced a lawsuit.  Ada Electric Cars sued the tax commission and its members saying the commission broke the law in making the changes to the tax credits. 

Devon Energy Corp. has given a $95-million line of credit to Oklahoma City, city government to help with a downtown makeover centered on the energy companies 50 story office tower project.  
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>76</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 9-23-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_9-23-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_9-23-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>471</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Plans for another 10 Commandments Monument, this time on the grounds of the LeFlore County Courthouse, have been put on hold.  County Commissioners delayed action on the project until a ruling from the Supreme Court on a similar case. 

OETA&#039;s Jason Doyle talks with Oklahoma Bankers about a recent national study that gave the state got a "C" grade for its support of asset building by families. The report highlights programs that provide matching money for a family savings program. 
  
An interim study begins at the state capitol on the rating system used by consumers as a guide on which nursing homes do the best job of caring for the elderly or disabled. 

OETA&#039;s Cathy Tatom talks one-on-one with an icon of the civil rights movement in America and around the world.  Dr. Richard Lapchick has championed racial equality in sports and through out society for decades. 

Fireworks dealers want the legislature to change the rules on burn bans issued by County Commissioners.  The dealers claim the Commissioners don&#039;t always follow all the legal requirements before issuing bans that impact the fireworks business. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>75</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 9-21-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_9-21-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_9-21-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>468</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[State and Federal railroad officials gathered in Oklahoma City today to explain to Oklahoma Transportation officials what it is going to take to tap into the billions of dollars set aside for high speed rail and other rail projects.  The message was clear, form partnerships with other states or forget about getting the cash. 

The body of 1st Lt. David Wright II is back in Oklahoma.  The Moore soldier was killed by a roadside bomb in Afghanistan along with several other members of his Stryker Unit.  A procession led by a hearse that held his remains, made its way through central Oklahoma this afternoon. 

A new national study gives the state a grade of "C" for the financial stability of it families.  The study concludes there is much more that policy makers could do to help the situation, namely invest more in education and increase access to health care. 

Historical markers, signs and new businesses are springing up along Route 66 in Oklahoma.  The "mother road" is seeing increased traffic now in part because of higher fees on toll roads. 

The latest adoption offering of wild horses and burrows in Pauls Valley failed to attract one person.  Federal officials in charge of the program blame the recession. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>74</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>Oklahoma News Report</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_09-23-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_09-23-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>469</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>73</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 9-22-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_9-22-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_9-22-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>470</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>72</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">HD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 9-18-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_9-18-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_9-18-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>466</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[Tulsa Public School officials say the ongoing state budget cuts are forcing cutbacks throughout their system and teachers may be laid off.   Tonight we focus on smaller school districts and how the budget cuts are impacting their operations. 

The EEOC has filed suit against Abercrombie and Fitch clothing store in Tulsa on behalf of a teenage Muslim girl who was reportedly refused employment because she wears a head scarf.   The suit claims the girl was told the scarf violates the stores, "look policy". 

If you own a Pikepass, by next summer the small white box will be replaced with a RFID sticker.  Turnpike Authority officials say it will reduce misread tolls and allows for agreements on tolls with Texas and Kansas. 

Another death from a meth lab explosion.  Last month, 29-year old Michael Miller was burned in the explosion in Bartlesville.  He died this week from those injuries in a Tulsa hospital.  

An In-Depth discussion with an official of Urban Neighbors, a group that is pushing for improved mass transit systems in central Oklahoma, about their view of the new MAPS 3 project which includes only a small portion of the funding for a electric trolley car system. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>71</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 9-14-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_9-14-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_9-14-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>464</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[During an average week in Oklahoma, eight babies will die before their first birthday.  A five state, three day conference is underway in Oklahoma City this week, looking for solutions to the infant mortality rate. 

One day before the latest state revenue figures are due out, state mental health officials are warning of impending cutbacks in services to as many as 65-thousand Oklahomans because of continued budget cuts. 

A former top aide to former Oklahoma Congressman Ernest Istook is expected to testify at the corruption trial of a former lobbyist.  Both federal prosecutors and defense attorneys have already talked in open court about lobbyists "showering" Istook with contributions and free meals and trips for his top aide. 

Rural ambulance service in Oklahoma is in serious financial straights.  In Skiatook, city officials are now asking that other municipalities that have been getting ambulance service for free start to pay their fair share.  
Some Oklahoma high schools now have new computer software to help coaches determine if one of their football players has suffered a concussion. 
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>70</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 9-11-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_9-11-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_9-11-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>463</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[On the 8th anniversary of 9-11, an Oklahoma terrorism expert says the day should serve as a reminder that the nation must remain vigilant in efforts to prevent future attacks. 

The Chief Justice of the State Supreme Court says he won&#039;t ask the board of Judicial Compensation to raise salaries because of the state&#039;s budget crisis. The Chief Justice says he has also trimmed the courts budget request for next fiscal year. 

The latest weekly rig count is out and the numbers went down in both the nation and Oklahoma.  The state had five fewer rigs working this last week compared to the week before. 

She was born a year ago, but now Zoe has left the nursery and is living with the rest of the Chimpanzees at the Oklahoma City Zoo.  Zoe is the first Chimp to be born at the zoo in 60 years.  
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>69</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 9-10-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_9-10-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_9-10-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>461</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[We talk with Oklahomans about their thoughts on the President&#039;s Speech last night to congress.  Most we talked with did not see the speech.
			The President of O.U.-Tulsa took part in an Internet Web-cast forum today on health care reform.  Dr. Gerry Clancy talked about how the O.U. School of Community Medicine is changing the way it practices medicine. 
			For students in the Oolagah-Talala public schools, lunch is just a finger print away. The use of the finger print scanner in schools has been banned elsewhere in the country. 
			The Chief of the Cherokee&#039;s and a Harvard law professor squared off today during the Federal Bar Association Convention, over the Freedman Issue.  
			The New American Banjo museum is now open for business in Bricktown.

The man who is credited with reviving the popularity of a truly American musical instrument was on hand for the grand opening.  We talk with Earl Scruggs tonight on the ONR. 



]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>68</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 9-8-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_9-8-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_9-8-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>458</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[   President Obama talked with school students across the nation today.  Oklahoma schools had different approaches on showing that speech because of parents who didn&#039;t want their children exposed to the President of the United States. 

  As natural gas prices continue to fall, the CEO of Chesapeake Energy remains bullish on his companies main product, predicting more companies are about to make the move to C-N-G.

  Imagine being able to go-online and get a price listing of surgery procedures.  OETA&#039;s Jason Doyle reports on a medical facility in Oklahoma that is providing that information right now. 

]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>66</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
		<track>
			<title>ONR 9-9-09</title>
			<ov:subtitle></ov:subtitle>
			<location>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/ONR_9-9-09.flv</location>
			<image>http://video.oeta.tv/onr/_thumbs/ONR_9-9-09.jpg</image>
			<identifier>459</identifier>
			<annotation><![CDATA[ Independent oil and gas producers and the state Farm Bureau are joining a federal lawsuit on the side of the state Tax Commission. The commission was sued by the Osage Indian Nation claiming all of Osage county is the tribe&#039;s reservation so any tribal member who works for the nation and lives in Osage county is exempt from state income taxes.

   The Oklahoma Conservation Commission broke ground in Garfield County today on a new water shed dam, the first new structure of its kind to be built in the U.S. with federal stimulus funds.  It is part of a new effort to reduce chronic flooding problems in the area.

   Despite pending lawsuits, work has begun to remove dirt and tear out the old passenger platforms that used to be home to the Union Station Rail Yard in Oklahoma City.  A new 10 lane I-40 link is being built in its place so the old Crosstown Expressway can be torn down. 

   A live interview tonight with the President of the OIPA to talk about what is going on in Oklahoma&#039;s energy business.  Mike Terry will address issues including the dumping of millions of gallons of Canadian oil that has been driving down the price of Oklahoma Crude.

   It&#039;s a dog&#039;s life.  Imagine being tied up with a short chain and forced to live in a small cage.  The Human Society wants to see new laws banning the practice of chaining dogs up.  The society is sponsoring a week long contest where contestants live for a week on a chain with only a small dog house for shelter. The winner gets a new car.
]]></annotation>
			<trackNum>64</trackNum>
			<ov:topics/>
			<meta rel="type">flv</meta>
			<meta rel="aspect">SD</meta>
		</track>
	</trackList>
</playlist>
